完
我的眼睛盯着那只动物。
I got eyes on the animal.
♪ 我们一起去大厅 ♪
♪ 为了让自己得到一个款待运行！去！ ♪
♪ 美味可吃的东西 ♪
♪ 爆米花不能被打败 ♪
♪ 起泡饮料只是花哨的 ♪
♪ 巧克力棒和糖果 ♪
♪ 所以让我们都去大厅给自己一个享受 ♪
什麽?
What?
让我出去!
Let me out!
保持稳定！
Keep it steady!
该死的，我看不出来。你看到了吗？
Damn, I don't see it. Do you see it?
安定下来，孩子。她不能永远跑。
Settle down, kid. She can't run forever.
恐龙就在我们的世界里。
Dinosaurs are in our world.
随着每一次对抗，我们都会更多地了解这个可怕的新现实。
And with every confrontation, we learn
more about this frightening new reality.
我们怎麽到这儿来的?
How did we get here?
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
自侏罗纪公园的致命事件以来，已经过去了三十年
It's been three decades
since the deadly events at Jurassic Park,
我们还没有找到一种方法让这些动物安全地生活在我们中间。
and we've yet to find a way
for these animals to live safely among us.
在努布拉尔岛长期休眠的火山毁灭性喷发之后
After the devastating eruption
of Isla Nublar's long-dormant volcano,
那些幸存下来的人被运送到大陆。
those who survived were transported
to the mainland.
许多较大的捕食者被捕获，
Many of the larger predators
were captured,
但剩下的生物散落在这里，
but the remaining creatures
scattered here,
在大石国家公园。
in Big Rock National Park.
虽然大多数人留在野外，但那些走向文明的人
While most remained in the wild,
those who made their way to civilization
努力适应陌生的条件。
struggled to adapt
to unfamiliar conditions.
地方当局警告说，这些动物是不可预测的
Local authorities have warned
the animals are unpredictable,
饥饿时，极度暴力。
and when hungry, extremely violent.
随着恐龙的跨境传播，全球黑市已经兴起。
As the dinosaurs spread across borders,
a global black market has risen.
他们不是我们的。走吧，你这个悲伤的，可怜的失败者！
- They're not ours.
- Go on, you sad, pathetic loser!
为了打击非法偷猎者日益增长的威胁
To combat the growing threat
of illegal poachers,
美国国会授予唯一的收藏权
the US Congress awarded
sole collection rights
到全球巨头生物科技 遗传学。
to the global giant Biosyn Genetics.
在生物科技，我们致力于这个想法
At Biosyn, we're dedicated to the idea
恐龙可以教会我们更多关于自己的知识。
that dinosaurs can teach us
more about ourselves.
首席运行官路易斯·道奇森 在义大利的白云石山脉 创建了一个避难所
CEO Lewis Dodgson has created
a sanctuary in Italy's Dolomite Mountains,
他希望在那里研究恐龙的古代免疫系统
where he hopes to study
the dinosaurs' ancient immune systems
具有独特的药物特性。
for unique pharmaceutical properties.
虽然生物科技认为我们可以负责任地处理遗传力量
While Biosyn believes
we can handle genetic power responsibly,
公众仍然持怀疑态度。
the public remains skeptical.
一些人指出，这些政府合同导致生物科技的利润大幅飙升。
Some note these government contracts have
led to massive spikes in Biosyn's profits.
关于一个神秘失踪的人类克隆体的谣言依然存在，
And rumors persist of a human clone
who mysteriously disappeared,
导致全球搜索。
leading to a worldwide search.
有些人认为她在基因上与夏洛特·洛克伍德 相同
Some believe she's genetically identical
to Charlotte Lockwood,
侏罗纪公园联合创始人本杰明·洛克伍德的已故女儿。
deceased daughter of Jurassic Park
co-founder, Benjamin Lockwood.
现在我们把这些动物从灭绝中带回来了
Now that we brought these animals
back from extinction,
我们能面对后果吗？
can we face the consequences?
我们是否对他们负责
Are we responsible for them,
还是应该让他们自己照顾自己？
or should they be left
to fend for themselves?
随着我们适应不断变化的世界
As we adapt to an ever-changing world,
我们必须找到这些问题的答案
we must find answers to these questions,
为了他们的安全以及我们自己的安全。
for their safely as well as for our own.
放手吧！
Let it go!
坚持!
Hold on!
我们在非法繁殖设施内。
We are inside
the illegal breeding facility.
幼鱼被关在笼子里，以降低成本。
The juveniles are kept in cages
to keep costs down.
这是中世纪的。
It's medieval.
克雷尔。
Claire.
你认为他为什麽与其他人分开？
Why do you think he's separated
from the rest?
我认为他不会成功。
I don't think he's gonna make it.
不。你在干什麽？我们可以报告这一点。
No. What are you doing?
We could report this.
DFW 需要几天时间进行调查。
The DFW takes days to investigate.
我们现在可以保存这个。
We can save this one now.
没关系。没关系，哥们。
It's okay. It's okay, buddy.
好。来吧。
Okay. Here we go.
不。不！
Nope. No!
- 电梯。
- 好。
- Lift.
- Okay.
- 支撑头部。
- 是的。
- Support the head.
- Yeah.
好。是的。
Okay. Yeah.
- 快点!
- 检查右侧。
- Hurry up!
- Check the right side.
- 跟我来。
- 走,走,走。
- With me.
- Go, go, go.
好的，来吧。来吧，我们走吧。
Okay, come on.
Come on, let's go.
- 坚持!
- 什麽?
- Hold on!
- To what?
妈的。
Shit.
克雷尔，我们要被枪杀了！
Claire, we're gonna get shot!
- 不！克雷尔！不，不，克雷尔！
- 天啊。
- No! Claire! No, no, Claire!
- Oh, God.
该死。
Oh, shit.
大家都好吗？
Everybody good?
- 不!
- No!
好。好吧，所以我想我们把这个送到 DFW
Okay. Okay, so I think
we get this one to the DFW,
然后我们再次击中它们。
and then we hit them again.
是的。是的，你看到了那个滋生地，对吧？
Yeah. Yeah, you saw
that breeding ground, right?
我们完成了。
We're done.
上周我接到了一个电话。
I got a call last week.
这是一项真正的工作，我可以做些什麽来有效地改变事情。
It's a real job, something I can do
to effectively change things.
- 我必须接受它。
- 他们需要我们
- I gotta take it.
- They need us.
你拯救这些恐龙是因为它们需要我们吗？
Are you saving these dinosaurs
because they need us,
还是你拯救他们来赦免自己？
or are you saving them
to absolve yourself?
克雷尔。我的意思是，这太疯狂了。
- Claire.
- I mean, this is crazy.
克雷尔
Claire,
你正在做正确的事情。
you're doing the right thing.
但是这个...这不再是这样做的方式。
But this... This isn't the way
to go about it anymore.
老实说，你需要一个善于被枪杀的人。
Honestly, you need someone
who's good at being shot at.
你和欧文不是还是一件奇怪的事情吗？
Aren't you and Owen still,
like, a weird thing?
- 这并不奇怪。
- 他的意思不是“怪异”。
- It's not that weird.
- He didn't mean "weird."
- 嗯 - 嗯
- 不。
- Mm-mmm.
- No.
呃，他的意思是，就象，令人惊讶。
Uh, he meant, like, surprising.
海亚！
Hyah!
让我们把他们带回家！
Let's bring 'em home!
海亚！
Hyah!
不。
No.
好,过来。
Okay, come here.
好。
Okay.
嘿 嘿。
Hey, hey.
我们会把你送到一个安全的地方。
We're gonna get you
someplace safe.
嘿。
Hey.
给你。
There you go.
是的。
Yeah.
妈的。
Shit.
偷猎是三到五。你们都知道。
Poaching's three to five.
Y'all know that.
看起来我们会把那只动物从你手上拿下来。
Looks like we'll be
taking that animal off your hands.
就象下界一样, 你会的。
Like hell you will.
好吧。看来我们的朋友不认识徽章。
All right. Seems our friend
don't recognize the badge.
鱼类和野生动物部。
Department of Fish and Wildlife.
我们正在围捕那只恐龙，以保证它自己的安全。
We're rounding up that dinosaur
for its own safety.
真有意思。
That's funny.
“因为我在这里的朋友，他们通常认识所有的新成员。
'Cause my friends here,
they typically know all the new recruits.
谢普，你还记得在迎新会上见过这些家伙吗？
Shep, do you remember meeting these guys
in orientation or not?
不。
Nope.
恐龙骨粉是为了什麽？3000一盎司？
Dinosaur bone powder goes for what?
3000 an ounce?
使这里的这种动物值得...
Makes this animal here worth about...
拍摄，500，000美元？
Shoot, $500,000?
你们怎麽想这个去，对吧？
How y'all want this to go, huh?
你的骨头对我来说不值一提。
Your bones ain't worth nothing to me.
嘿，兄弟。
Hey, brother.
他没有撒谎。
He ain't lying.
再见了。
I'll see you around.
以前从未见过你从战斗中走开。
Never seen you walk away
from a fight before.
是的。
Yeah.
我有义务。
I got obligations.
你不应该在学校吗？
Shouldn't you be in school?
我在家接受教育。
I'm homeschooled.
是这样吗？
That so?
家在哪里？
And where's home?
我不知道!
I don't know!
哇!
Whoa!
最好不要站在那里，伙计。
Better not stand there, man.
天啊
Holy crap.
到底是什麽，伙计？
What in the world, man?
所以，恐龙...
So, the dinosaurs...
嘿。
Hey.
你去哪儿了?
Where you been?
- 无处。
- 你在燃烧什麽？
Nowhere.
What are you burning?
哦，没什麽。只是一些旧毯子。
Oh, nothing. Just some old blankets.
你确定你没有经过桥吗？
You sure you didn't go past the bridge?
这就是你认为我在撒谎时给我的眼神。
That's the look you give me
when you think I'm lying.
- 嗯，是吗？
- 不。
- Well, are you?
- No.
Maisie，你几乎到处都在找，但在这里。
Maisie, you're literally looking
everywhere but here.
我说我没有经过桥。
I said I didn't go past the bridge.
麦茜，
Maisie,
我们可以重新开始吗？
can we start over?
我知道，克莱尔。有些人会做任何事情来找到我。
I know, Claire. There are people out there
who'll do anything to find me.
我没有生气
I'm not angry.
- 这意味着你不必生气。
- 我没有生气
- That means you don't have to be angry.
- I'm not angry.
- 我可以照顾好自己。
- 嘿。
- I can take care of myself.
- Hey.
我们互相依赖是可以的。这就是人们所做的。
It's okay for us to depend on each other.
That's what people do.
我怎麽知道人们在做什麽？
How would I know what people do?
在过去四年里，我唯一和你交谈过的人就是你们俩。
The only people I've spoken to
in the past four years are you both.
此外，无论如何，我甚至不是一个真正的人。
Besides,
I'm not even a real person anyway.
- 什麽?
- 我是由别人做的。
- What?
- I was made from someone else.
我不是我。
I'm not me.
你是唯一曾经的你。
You are the only you who ever was.
什麽?
What?
- 不- 否。
- 这真的是陈词滥调吗？
- N-No.
- Was that, like, really corny?
太陈腐了。
It was so corny.
- 我们能保持这种关系吗？
- 答应不了。
- Can we keep that between us?
- Can't promise that.
- 嘿,孩子。
- 你好。
- Hey, kid.
- Hello.
对不起,我迟到了。
Sorry I'm late.
啊.
Aw.
你闻起来象马。
You smell like horses.
- 嗯。
- 哦，你喜欢这样，是吗？
- Mmm.
- Oh, you like that, do ya?
- 是的。是的。
- 哦。
- I do. Yeah.
- Oh.
好。嗯...
Okay. Um...
我要去做晚饭。
I'm gonna make dinner.
一切都还好吧?
Everything okay?
她又进城了。
She went into town again.
啊，这个孩子。你和她谈过吗？
Ah, this kid.
Did you talk to her?
我试过了。
I tried.
我会和她谈谈。
I'll talk to her.
呼吸缓慢。别着急。
Slow breaths. Take your time.
嘿。从自己身上切开。
Hey. Cut away from yourself.
哇!
Whoa!
想知道如何赢得一场刀战吗？
Wanna know how to win
a knife fight?
你必须让自己被削减。
You gotta let yourself get cut.
确保他们正在切割可有可无的东西
Make sure they're cutting
something dispensable
当你在切割一些重要的东西时。
while you're cutting something vital.
然后说一些很酷的话，比如...
And then say something cool like...
“错姑娘，错时间。”
"Wrong girl, wrong time."
错误的女孩，错误的时间。
Wrong girl, wrong time.
喔!
Whoo!
- 冷冰冰的。
- 正确的！
- Stone-cold.
- Right?
我不会惹她。不可能。
- I would not mess with her.
- No way.
听。我们可能应该谈谈你进城的事情。
Listen. We should probably
talk about you going into town.
我没有。
I don't...
我不认为你明白被困在这里有多糟糕。
I don't think you understand
how bad it is being trapped here.
你没有被困在这里。我们只是不信任人。
You're not trapped here.
We just don't trust people.
不，你只是不信任我。
No, you just don't trust me.
然后你希望我信任你。
And then you expect me to trust you.
- 为什麽我不能有任何自由？
- 因为你不能。
- Why can't I have any freedom?
- Because you can't.
这真是太好了。
That went great.
发生了什麽事情?
What is happening?
- 她14岁。
- 是的。
- She's 14.
- Yeah.
你还记得那是什麽感觉。
You remember what that was like.
我愿意。
I do.
我们不能永远把她留在这里。
We can't keep her here forever.
如果我们不弄清楚这一点，她会比桥走得更远。
If we don't figure this out, she's gonna
go a lot farther than the bridge.
如果他们找到她，我们再也不会见到她了。
If they find her,
we're never gonna see her again.
我们必须保护她。这就是我们的工作。这就是我们要做的。
We gotta protect her. That's our job.
That's what we're gonna do.
如何保护她？
Protect her how?
把她锁在里面？
By locking her inside?
她有问题。
She's got questions.
你知道的？我们无法回答的问题。
You know? Questions we can't answer.
她想知道自己是谁。
She wants to know who she is.
夏洛特·洛克伍德是谁。
Who Charlotte Lockwood was.
跟踪格雷迪到他家。
Tracked Grady to his house.
你是对的。猛禽有一个少年。
You were right. Raptor's got a juvenile.
但是听着，还有别的东西。
But listen, there's something else.
我找到了你一直追求的那个女孩。
I found that girl you've been after.
给你。
Here you go.
谢谢你的来。
Thanks for coming.
不知道该给谁打电话。
Wasn't sure who to call.
鱼和野生动物甚至不想看到它，如果它不是恐龙。
Fish and Wildlife didn't even want
to see it if it wasn't a dinosaur.
是的，好吧，他们得到了所有的注意力。
Yeah, well,
they get all the attention.
你们想改变采样图
You guys want to vary
the sampling plots
各一百码？
a hundred yards each?
这些是你的学生？
These your students?
是的。我们一直在研究工业化农业对环境的影响。
Yeah. We've been looking into the impact
of industrial farming on the environment.
所以，就在我们的小巷里。
So, this is right up our alley.
他们击中了该县的60个田地。
They hit 60 fields
in the county.
你以前见过这样的东西吗？
You seen anything like
this before?
不。不是这样的。
No. Not like this.
他们一直在离开整个中西部的退化田野。
They've been leaving degraded fields
all across the Midwest.
首先，这些大公司试图杀死所有的昆虫，现在这个。
First these big companies try to kill off
all the insects, now this.
那是你的土地吗？
Is that your land?
那是贝内特一家的玉米。蝗虫没有吃掉它。
That's the Bennetts' corn.
The locusts didn't eat that.
你种下的种子和班纳特是一样的吗？
You plant the same seed
as the Bennet is?
不。
No.
我们是独立的。
We're independent.
他们使用生物合成种子。
They use Biosyn seed.
是的，我敢打赌他们会。
Yeah, I bet they do.
你说你抓到了一个活的？
You say you caught a live one?
孩子们，这是艾莉·萨特勒博士。
Kids, this is Dr. Ellie Sattler.
她是来自大学的科学家。
She's a scientist from the university.
虫子科学家？
A bug scientist?
呃，差不多吧。
Uh, sort of.
我从很久以前就开始研究植物，
I study plants from a long time ago,
这有助于我现在弄清楚如何保护植物和土壤。
and that helps me figure out
how to protect plants and soil now.
哇。看啊。
Wow. Look at that.
很酷吧？
Pretty cool, huh?
这称为字段定序器
This is called a field sequencer,
它説明我随时随地读取 DNA。
and it helps me read DNA
everywhere I am.
我要把这个棉签放进他的嘴里。
I'm gonna put this swab in his mouth.
干得好。
Good job.
现在，我需要带你的小伙伴去公路旅行。
And now, I need to take your little buddy
on a road trip.
你把它带到哪里去？
Where are you taking it?
我需要第二种意见。
I need a second opinion.
嘿，玛德琳？是的？
- Hey, Madeline?
- Yeah?
我们只需要清理这个小圆柱体。
We just gotta clean out
this little cylinder.
好。让她慢慢下来。
Okay. Let her down slow.
- 明白了?
- 是的。
- Got it?
- Yeah.
容易。
Easy.
让我们开始填充另一边。
Let's start padding that other side.
就在那里。我在上面。
Just about there. I'm on it.
我们为什麽要挖掘？
Why do we dig?
因为古生物学是科学，而科学是关于真理的。
Because paleontology is science,
and science is about the truth.
这些岩石里有真理。
And there is truth in these rocks.
停止。
Stop.
它在这里说霸王龙有一个很小的大脑。
It says here
that the T. rex had a tiny brain.
好吧，事实证明，霸王龙比我们想象的要聪明得多。
Well, it turns out that T. rex
was way smarter than we thought.
能够记忆，忠诚。
Capable of memory, of loyalty.
那是霸王龙。
That's a T. rex.
他们从90年代开始就已经存在了。
They've been around
since, like, the '90s.
我不明白为什麽我们在这里挖骨头。
I don't get why we're here
digging up bones.
这似乎有点随机。
It just seems kinda random.
正确的？
Right.
授予!
Grant!
你会想看到这个。
You're gonna want to see this.
伙计们，你能帮帮我吗？
Guys, can you help me?
我会把它打包出来。我会确保没有其他人越过它。
I'll pack it out.
I'll make sure nobody else crosses it.
艾莉·萨特勒。
Ellie Sattler.
艾伦·格兰特。
Alan Grant.
你看起来一样。
You look the same.
而这个地方，它是如此...
And this place, it's so...
所以，呃...你。
so, uh... you.
对不起。如果我知道你要来，我会...
I'm sorry. If I'd known
you were coming, I would've...
呃...
Uh...
我能给你买点什麽吗？啤酒或...
Can I get you something?
A beer or...
嗯，好吧，也许不是在上午10点，而是冰茶或...
Um, well, maybe not at 10:00 a.m.,
but iced tea or...
茶。是的。
Tea. Yeah.
茶。我能做到。
Tea. I can do that.
在进去的路上看到很多游客。
Saw a lot of tourists
on the way in.
好吧，资金已经枯竭了，所以有人必须为这一切买单。
Well, the funding's dried up,
so somebody's gotta pay for all this.
正确的。谢谢。
Right. Thank you.
我读了你关于土壤科学和再生农业的文章。
I read your articles about soil science
and regenerative farming.
真棒。
That's great.
谢谢。
Thanks.
给了我一些改变的希望。
Gave me grounds
for some hope for a change.
还有一个关于生长藻类的。
And the one about growing algae.
嗯！艾伦，太神奇了。
Mmm! Alan, it's amazing.
它是一种完全可行的碳中性燃料。
It's a totally viable
carbon-neutral fuel.
这太不可思议了。我们的答案就在我们的海洋和土壤中。
It's incredible. Our answers
are in our oceans and in our soil.
当然，这需要工作，但我们正处于灭绝的边缘。
Sure, it's gonna take work,
but we're on the verge of extinction.
我的上帝。我们该怎麽办？只是坐在那里？
My God. What are we gonna do?
Just sit around?
不在我的手表上。
Not on my watch.
什麽?
What?
不，没有。我只是。
No, nothing. I just...
就象听你说话一样。
Just like listening to you is all.
所以，你自己在这里吗？
So, you're here on your own?
是的。靠我自己。
Yeah, yeah. On my own.
你的孩子怎麽样？
How are your kids?
嗯。
Mmm.
了不起。长大了。这太令人震惊了。
Amazing. Grown. It's shocking.
他们都在上大学。你能相信吗？
They're both in college.
Can you believe that?
而马克呢？
And Mark?
结束了。
It's over.
哦。
Oh.
哦，我很抱歉听到这个消息。
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
没关系。
It's okay.
我又回到了我身边。
I'm back to me.
还有我的工作。你知道，这是...
And my work. You know, it's...
真棒。
That's great.
很好。是的。我终于孤身一人了。
It's good. It is. I'm alone at last.
激动人心的时刻。
Exciting times.
是的，我过着艾伦·格兰特的生活。
Yeah, I'm living the Alan Grant life.
- 只是...
- 可能会很孤独。
- It's just...
- Can be lonely.
...如此自由。
...so freeing.
艾莉。
Ellie.
你一路走来不是为了赶上，现在，你呢？
You didn't come out all this way
just to catch up, now, did you?
嗯，那是蝗虫。
Well, that's a locust.
下颌骨，翅膀，胸部，但是...
Mandibles, wings, thorax, but...
上帝啊，它的大小是巨大的。
God, the size of it is massive.
它具有自白垩纪以来已经灭绝的基因。
It has genes that have been extinct
since the Cretaceous.
成群结队的农作物从爱荷华州到德克萨斯州正在大量减少。
And swarms of them are decimating crops
from Iowa to Texas.
太可怕了，对吧？
Terrifying, right?
从几百人开始。
Started as a few hundred.
到夏末可能会有数百万人。
There could be millions
by the end of the summer.
如果他们继续前进，就没有谷物来喂养鸡，牛。
If they keep going, there'll be
no grain to feed chickens, cattle.
整个食物链将崩溃。
The entire food chain
would collapse.
好吧，它显然是设计好的，但是为什麽有人会这样做呢？
Well, it's clearly designed,
but why would anyone do that?
他们正在吃的作物中没有一个是生物合成种子。
None of the crops they're eating
are Biosyn seed.
生物合成。
Biosyn.
你是说生物科技做了这个吗？
You're saying Biosyn made this?
我的意思是，他们想要控制世界的食物供应不会让我感到震惊。
I mean, it would not shock me that they
wanna control the world's food supply.
在几百万人挨饿之前。
Not before a few million starve.
是的，那是什麽说法？我们离无政府状态只有三顿饭吗？
Yeah, what is that saying?
How we're three meals away from anarchy?
如果我们不阻止他们，您可以选择最后三餐。
If we don't stop them,
you can pick your last three meals.
那麽，你为什麽要把它带给我呢？
So, why are you bringing it to me?
我需要具体的证据来证明生物科技对这一切负责。
I need concrete evidence
Biosyn's responsible for all this.
我需要去他们的避难所，从那里的另一只蝗虫身上获取DNA。
I need to go to their sanctuary
and get DNA from another locust there.
但我需要一个见证人。
But I need a witness.
艾伦。
Alan.
你得到尊重。人们相信你。
You command respect.
People believe you.
艾莉。
Ellie.
你知道我为什麽在这里。很安静。我完成了所有这些。
You know why I'm here.
It's quiet. I'm done with all that.
你是？好。
Are you? Okay.
好吧，对不起，艾伦。
Well, I'm sorry, Alan.
没有人再得到那麽奢侈了，甚至连你也不行。
Nobody gets that luxury anymore,
not even you.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
你是我信任的人。
You're the one I trust.
这个生物科学保护区，什麽，离任何地方一百英里？
This Biosyn sanctuary is, what,
a hundred miles from anywhere?
你是怎麽进入那里的？
How do you even get in there?
我收到了他们内部哲学家的邀请。
I got an invite
from their in-house philosopher.
这些天做混沌人似乎有很多钱。
Seems there's a lot of money
in being a chaotician these days.
他只是碰巧突然邀请你？
And he just happened
to invite you out of the blue?
他说有些事情我想看到。
He said there were things I'd wanna see.
嗯嗯。
Uh-huh.
你来了还是什麽？
You coming or what?
很清楚！
It's clear!
继续前进。很好。
Keep it going. That's good.
在大陆捕获的每一只动物都经过这里
Every animal captured
on the mainland comes through here
在运往生物科技在多洛米蒂山脉的避难所之前。
before shipping out
to Biosyn's sanctuary in the Dolomites.
我们给他们医疔照顾，并确保他们健康离开。
We give them medical attention
and make sure they leave healthy.
如此多的安全性。
So much security.
这些只是你看到的那些。
Those are just the ones you see.
很多阴暗的类型都想要这些家伙。
A lot of shady types out there
want these guys.
- 嘿。
- 你的飞机只是在加油。
- Hey.
- Your plane's just fueling up.
生物科技是一个艰难的邀请。你们一定认识某个人。
Biosyn's a tough invite.
You guys must know somebody.
- 你介意我...
- 答案是肯定的。
- Do you mind if I...
- Of course.
你好。
Hello.
你看到我了吗？你跟着我。
You see me?
You follow me.
我们从一个非法繁殖农场救出了这些家伙。
We rescued these guys
from an illegal breeding farm
几周前在内华达州。
in Nevada a few weeks ago.
关闭整个地方。匿名提示。
Shut the whole place down.
Anonymous tip.
好女孩。是的。是的。
Good girl. Yes. Yes.
艾伦。你永远不会习惯它。
Alan. You never get used to it.
好。我们很好。关闭它！
Okay. We're good. Close it up!
- 当心。
- 谢谢。再见。
- Take care.
- Thank you. Bye.
好。
Okay.
嘿。
Hey.
你看起来就象蓝色一样。
You look just like Blue.
这?
This?
你想试试吗？
You wanna try it?
好。
Okay.
嗯.
Huh.
麦茜，别动。
Maisie, don't move.
嘿,女孩。
Hey, girl.
远离麻烦？
Staying out of trouble?
她生了一个孩子。不可能。
She had a baby. That's impossible.
- 退后。
- 她不会伤害我们，对吧？
- Back up.
- She won't hurt us, right?
你该死的，她会的。
You're damn right she will.
呼吸吧。
Just breathe.
- 如果你不这样做，她会认为你很害怕。
- 我很害怕。
- If you don't, she'll think you're scared.
- I am scared.
不。她不需要知道这一点。
Nah.
She doesn't need to know that.
她的巢穴一定在附近。麦茜，进去吧。
Her nest has got to be nearby.
Maisie, get inside.
- 我一起去。
- 我刚才说什麽了？
- I'm coming with you.
- What did I just say?
- 我们得搬家了
- 还没有。我们需要这个女孩。
- We gotta move.
- Not yet. We need the girl.
嘿,怎么了?
Hey, what's up?
哇。
Wow.
梅西?
Maisie?
嗯嗯嗯
Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
你要去哪里?
Where you going?
你不能把我留在这里。你不是我的母亲。
You can't keep me here.
You're not my mother.
她要离开家了。
She's leaving the house.
上车！加油！我们走吧！
Get in the truck!
Come on! Let's go!
明白了!
Got it!
- 系紧！
- 坚持。
- Tie it down!
- Hold on.
加油。我们走吧!
Come on. Let's go!
- 进去!
- 加油!
- Get in!
- Come on!
让我们离开这里。
Let's get out of here.
你是谁?
Who are you?
克雷尔!
Claire!
他们找到了她。
They found her.
什麽？他们是谁？
What? Who are they?
偷猎 者。我在周围见过他们。
Poachers. I've seen them around.
领导者是一个真正的混蛋。
Leader's a real shit-heel.
他一定认出了我，跟着我来到这里。
He must have recognized me,
followed me here.
- 她在哪?
- 去拿卡车。
- Where is she?
- Go get the truck.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
天啊。
Oh, God.
- 欧文！
- 嘿。不。
- Owen!
- Hey. No.
他们也带走了她的孩子。
They took her kid too.
我要把她找回来。
I am gonna get her back.
我向你保证。
I promise you that.
加油。
Come on.
我知道该给谁打电话。
I know who to call.
拜托，拜托！不 不！
Please, please! No, no!
今年，伙计。下一步是什麽？
This year, man.
What's next?
历史？
Historically?
呃，黑暗，血腥，火雨。我想到青蛙。
Uh, darkness, blood, rain of fire.
I think frogs.
无论如何，我们不会存在太久。
We're not gonna be around
for much longer anyway.
内布拉斯加州的这些蝗虫即将将其包裹起来。
These locusts in Nebraska
are about to wrap it up.
他们吃玉米，小麦。
They're eating the corn, wheat.
基本上我们所有的食物和食物的食物。
Basically all of our food
and our food's food.
所以，我们可以告别这个。
So, we can say goodbye to this.
你好?
Hello?
佛兰克林。是我。你在工作吗？
Franklin. It's me. You at work?
好吧，你是这里感兴趣的话题
Okay, you're kind of
a subject of interest around here,
所以我不能真的和你说话。
so I can't really be talking to you.
加油。我有麻烦了。我真的需要你的説明。请。
Come on. I'm in trouble.
I really need your help. Please.
是的，我可能会失去工作，
Yeah, and I could lose my job,
你知道我没有资格做其他任何事情。
and you know I'm not qualified
to do anything else.
我们在外面。
We're outside.
让我跟他谈谈
Let me talk to him.
- 那个他？
- 就是他。
- That him?
- That's him.
名字的雷恩·德拉库尔。真正的工作。
Name's Rainn Delacourt.
Real piece of work.
他会拿什麽？
What'd he take?
我们非常关心的事情。
Something we care about
very much.
该死。我告诉过你会有人来找她。
Oh, shit. I told you somebody
would come looking for her.
你不能只带一个人，克雷尔。
You can't just take a person, Claire.
- 我们别无选择。
- 在法律的眼中不是。
- We had no choice.
- Not in the eyes of the law.
这家伙不是法律。告诉我们如何找到他。
This guy is not the law.
Tell us how to find him.
你从哪里给我打电话？
Where'd you call me from?
我们在德拉库尔的行动内部有一个人。
We have a man on the inside
of Delacourt's operation.
明天某个时候在马尔他有一个交易所。现金用于货物。
There's an exchange in Malta
sometime tomorrow. Cash for cargo.
她和他在一起吗？
Was she with him?
没有提到，但我们已经有人在当地了。
There's no mention,
but we have people on the ground already.
其中之一你知道。
One of them you know.
我们中的很多人在公园倒塌后被中央情报局招募。
A lot of us got recruited by the CIA
after the park went down.
巴里现在的法国情报。
Barry's French intelligence now.
我要和他谈谈。
I need to talk to him.
你不能只是打电话给他。他是深深的掩护。
You can't just call him.
He's deep cover.
看，一旦我们在马尔他制作半身像
Look, once we make
the bust in Malta,
我们的人会看看德拉库尔是否知道她在哪里。
our guys will see
if Delacourt knows where she is.
我们的人。不是你。
Our guys. Not you.
答应我，你不会穿着背心进去，把一切都搞砸了。
Promise me you won't go in there
with your vest and mess everything up.
我为什麽要那麽做?
Why would I do that?
看，你们俩都疯了
Look, you guys are both crazy,
但你似乎是好父母，或者你想成为的任何东西。
but you seem like you're good parents,
or whatever you're trying to be.
她很幸运能有你。
She's lucky to have you.
不要被杀，好吗？
Don't get killed, okay?
我想我们差不多做到了。
I think we're almost there.
是的。
Yeah.
萨特勒博士。格兰特博士。
Dr. Sattler. Dr. Grant.
- 拉姆齐·科尔，通信。
- 哦 嘿。
- Ramsay Cole, Communications.
- Oh, hey.
我必须警告你，每个人都很高兴有你。
I have to warn you,
everyone's so excited to have you.
你们绝对是这里的传奇人物。
You guys are absolute legends
around here.
嗯，你一定是把我们和别人搞混了。
Mmm. You must be confusing us
with somebody else.
你知道，你们仍然和玛律科姆博士如此亲密，这真是太好了。
You know, it's great that you guys
are still so close with Dr. Malcolm.
我的意思是，有时你遇到你的英雄，他们让你失望，
I mean, sometimes you meet your heroes
and they disappoint you,
但他正是你想要他成为的样子。
but he's exactly the way
you'd want him to be.
我的意思是，这种思想的动力。这太不可思议了。
I mean, such motility of thought.
It's incredible.
你和他一起花了多少时间？
How much time
have you spent with him?
呃，好吧，我知道这是讽刺，但老实说，还不够。
Uh, well, I know that was sarcastic,
but honestly, not enough.
拜托。在你之后。注意你的头。
Oh, please. After you.
And watch your head.
生物科技早在90年代就为琥珀矿床购买了这片土地。
Biosyn bought this land
for the amber deposits back in the '90s.
但我们已经设法把它变成了一个安全的避风港。
But we've managed
to turn it into a safe haven
约20种流离失所的物种。
for about 20 displaced species.
第一代来自索尔纳。大多数努布拉尔恐龙也在这里。
First generation came from Sorna.
Most of the Nublar dinosaurs are here too.
花了三年的鱼和野生动物来捕捉霸王龙。
Took Fish and Wildlife three years
to catch the T. rex.
- 霸王龙来了？
- The...
- The T. rex is here?
哦，是的。是的。
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
就在你们之前到达。
Arrived just before you guys.
空中威慑系统，主动。
Aerial deterrent system, active.
限制空气空间。保护空气中的生命。
Restricted air space.
Protects the airborne life.
将翼龙保持在500英尺以下。
Keeps the pterosaurs below 500 feet.
空降？
Airborne?
那是无畏号吗？
Is that Dreadnoughtus?
什麽?
What?
很漂亮，对吧？
Beautiful, right?
这个名字的意思是“无所畏惧”。好吧，我想你知道的。
The name means "fear nothing."
Well, I guess you know that.
- 他们吃什麽？
- 山楂和蕨类植物。
- What do they graze on?
- Hawthorn and fern.
都是土着的。除了鹿群之外，什麽都没有放养。
All indigenous. Nothing stocked
except for the deer population.
对于顶级捕食者来说，这是一个很棒的夹层物种。
It's a great mezzanine species
for the apex predator.
顶级捕食者？
The apex predator?
巨龙。
Giganotosaurus.
至少现在是这样。
At least for now.
你不让人们进来，对吧？
You don't let people in there, right?
呃，不。我们。。。我们的研究...
Uh, no. Our... Our research...
我们的研究前哨完全连接在地下。
Our research outposts are connected
completely underground.
如果有必要，我们可以远程放牧动物
If we have to,
we can just herd the animals remotely
使用直接向大脑发送电信号的神经植入物。
using a neuro-implant that sends
electrical signals directly to the brain.
喜欢冲击？
Like shocks?
呃。。。n-不，象信号一样。
Uh... n-no, like signals.
是不是有点让你觉得有点...
Doesn't it strike you as a little bit...
- 残酷？
- 残酷。
- Cruel?
- Cruel.
你知道侏罗纪公园的电围栏里有多少电压吗？
Do you know how much voltage was
in the electric fences at Jurassic Park?
是的。
Yeah.
请与伊恩·玛律科姆博士在中午在演讲厅
Please join Dr. Ian Malcolm
at noon in the lecture hall
遗传力量伦理学。
for the Ethics of Genetic Power.
上帝啊，每个人都那麽年轻。
God, everyone's so young.
嗯，吸引最优秀和最聪明的人是我们精神的一部分。
Well, it is part of our ethos
to attract the best and brightest.
医生。
Doctors.
受人尊敬，着名的萨特勒博士。格兰特博士。你好。
Respected, renowned Dr. Sattler.
Dr. Grant. Hi.
哇，这很大。我是路易斯。
Wow, this is big. I'm Lewis.
- 道奇森。是的。
- 你好。
- Dodgson. Yeah.
- Hi.
- 你是路易斯·道奇森？
- 我是。你好？
- You're Lewis Dodgson?
- I am. How do you do?
我们没想到会在这里见到你。
We didn't expect
to actually see you here.
好吧，我不会在其他地方。
Well, I wouldn't be anywhere else.
你会吗？不。
- Would you?
- No.
我的意思是，你在这里看到的人正在改变世界。
I mean, the people you see here
are changing the world.
你会介意我们，嗯...
Would you mind if we, um...
- 只是为了...这将意味着很多。
- 哦。
- Just to... It would mean a lot.
- Oh.
你想吗，嗯...
Do you wanna, um...
- 哦，太好了。非常感谢。
- 哦。
- Oh, great. Thank you so much.
- Oh.
- 很好。很好。谢谢。
- 好。
- That's good. That's good. Thanks.
- Okay.
所以，你今天将看到一些非凡的事情。
So, you are going to see
some remarkable things today.
我们正在释放基因组的真正力量。
We are unlocking the true power
of the genome.
我们非常接近。相信我。
We're this close. Believe me.
你会从中发财。
You'll make a fortune with that.
不，这与钱无关。
No, it's not about money.
不，我们已经确定了古DNA的数十种应用。
No, we've already identified dozens
of applications for paleo-DNA.
我们谈论的是癌症，阿尔茨海默氏症，自身免疫性。
We're talking about cancer,
Alzheimer's, autoimmune.
我们将拯救生命。
We will be saving lives.
- 但。。。嘘。
- 我敢打赌。
- But... shh.
- I bet.
嗯，无论如何，我希望我能带你一起去，但是，呃，这是......
Um, anyway, I wish I could
take you around myself, but, uh, it's...
所以，你和拉姆齐在一起的能力已经很强了。
So, you're in more-than-capable hands
with Ramsay.
他基本上是一个年轻的我。
He's basically a young me.
只有更聪明，呃，更高。
Only smarter and, uh, taller.
你有食物吗？
Do you have food?
- 比如，我的一个酒吧？
- 赦？嗯......
- Like, one of my bars?
- Pardon? Um...
不，没关系。我-我会找到一些东西。
No, never mind.
I-I'll find something.
所以，我想稍后再做更多这样的事情，如果我们，嗯......
So, I want to do more of this
later on, if we, um...
哦！我们为您预订了一个私人吊舱...
Oh! We booked you
a private pod...
- 正确的。
- ...为了外出旅行，所以...
- Right.
- ...for the trip out, so...
真漂亮。你会爱上它。穿过洞穴和一切。
It's beautiful. You'll love it.
Through the caverns and everything.
你最好快点。玛律科姆上场了。
You better hurry. Malcolm's on.
他有点逆势，但我喜欢他。
He's a bit of a contrarian,
but I like him.
他让我们保持警剔。无论如何。
He keeps us on our toes. Anyway.
谢谢你来到这里。它。。。
Thank you for being here. It's...
好。思，请跟我来。
Okay. Um, follow me, please.
什麽?
What?
人类不再享有安全或自由的权利
Human beings have no more right
to safety or liberty
比这个星球上的任何其他生物都要多。
than any other creature
on this planet.
我们不仅缺乏对自然的统治
We not only lack dominion over nature,
我们服从于它。
we're subordinate to it.
现在，我们在这里
And now, here we are
有机会在我们的指尖改写生活。
with the opportunity to rewrite life
at our fingertips.
就象核电一样
And just like nuclear power,
没有人知道基因工程会发生什麽
nobody knew what to expect
with genetic engineering,
但他们按下按钮，希望得到最好的
but they pressed the button
and hoped for the best,
就象你现在所做的那样。
just like you are doing now.
是的。你。
Yep. You.
你控制着我们在地球上生存的未来。
You control the future
of our survival on planet Earth.
根据你的说法，解决方案是遗传力。
According to you,
the solution is genetic power.
但同样的力量可能会破坏粮食供应
But that same power
could devastate the food supply,
制造新的疾病，进一步改变气候。
create new diseases,
alter the climate even further.
意想不到的后果时有发生。
Unforeseen consequences occur.
每一次，每一次...
And every time, every single time...
我们都表现得很惊讶？
we all act surprised?
因为在内心深处
Because deep down,
我不认为我们中的任何一个人真的相信这些危险是真实的。
I don't think that any of us actually
believe that these dangers are real.
为了激发革命性的变革
In order to instigate
revolutionary change,
我们必须改变人类的意识。
we must transform human consciousness.
喔!
Whoo!
是的!
Yeah!
- 可能是？
- 玛律科姆博士？
- May am?
- Dr. Malcolm?
非常好。给你。
Very good. There you go.
我不想对我的朋友粗鲁。谢谢。
I don't want to be rude
to my friends. Thank you.
在我出去的路上抓住我。谢谢大家。
Catch me on my way out.
Thanks, everybody.
看看你
Look at you,
看着我，看着你。
and look at me, and look at you.
哇......这太笨拙了。
Wha... This is so trippy.
你看起来做得很好。
You look like you're doing well.
嗯，我有五个孩子，你知道，我比生活本身更崇拜他们，所以......
Well, I got five kids, you know,
whom I adore more than life itself, so...
费用加起来。
expenses add up.
你？艾伦，你是...您有任何家庭或...
You? Alan, are you...
You have any family or...
- 不。
- 所以，我需要和你谈谈。
- No.
- So, I need to talk to you.
是的，我也需要和你谈谈。私自。
Yeah, I need to talk to you too.
Privately.
你们俩经常说话吗？
Do you two talk a lot?
- 他溜进了我的私信。
- 他做了什麽?
- He slid into my DMs.
- He did what?
- 这很紧急，伊恩。
- 你做了什麽?
- It's urgent, Ian.
- What did you do?
七分钟到午夜的东西。
Seven minutes to midnight stuff.
末日时锺可能已经过时了
The Doomsday Clock might be
about out of time,
但是，正如他们所说，在永恒的虚无之前，它总是最黑暗的。
but, as they say, it's always darkest
just before eternal nothingness.
什麽?
What?
蝗虫随着白垩纪时代的DNA而改变。
Locusts altered with Cretaceous-era DNA.
那不是我的领域。但是，如果这些东西继续成倍增加
- That's not my field.
- But if these things continue to multiply,
我们谈论的是级联系统范围的效果，伊恩。
we're talking about
cascading system-wide effects, Ian.
天哪，这是一种拖累。
Gosh, that's a drag.
- 你怎么了?
- “拖拽”？
- What is the matter with you?
- "Drag"?
为什麽，你想让我做些特别的事情吗？
Why, is there something special
you wanted me to do?
- 给一个该死的怎麽样？
- 你知道太多了，不在乎。
- How about give a damn?
- You know too much not to care.
嘿，多年来我一直坚定地表达了我的意见。
Hey, I gave my opinion
robustly for years.
不出所料，我们人类努力的总和导致了我们的毁灭
As expected, the sum of our human
endeavors has led to our annihilation,
现在唯一的玩法就是花点时间，呃......
and the only play now
is to take the time we have left and, uh...
你知道，就象我们一直做的那样，浪费它。
you know,
just like we always do, squander it.
老实说，伊恩，那是胡说八道。
Honestly, Ian, that's bullshit.
我能给你们一些乔吗？
Can I offer you guys some joe?
泰勒，拜托，两杯卡布奇诺。
Tyler, please, two cappuccinos.
我不想要卡布奇诺。
I don't want a cappuccino.
我可以做，比如，一个科尔塔多或玛奇朵...
I could do, like, a cortado
or macchiato...
相信我，这真的很难，时差。这将使您振作起来。
Trust me, it's real tough, that jet lag.
This is gonna perk you right up.
蝗虫是一个名为六足同盟的大型项目的一部分。
The locusts are part of a larger project
called Hexapod Allies.
- 我...
- 你对他们的意图是正确的。
- I...
- You're right about their intent.
六周前，我开始听到谣言。
I started hearing rumors
six weeks ago.
我读了你关于颓废的文章，把两个和两个放在一起。
I read your piece on decadence
and put two and two together.
- 我没有提高嗓门。
- 你开始这样做了。它正在逐渐增加。
- I was not raising my voice.
- You're beginning to. It's crescendoing.
它们正在疯狂地扩散。
They're proliferating wildly.
它们的持续时间比他们应该的长三到四倍。
They're lasting three,
four times longer than they should.
我所有的模型都指向全球生态崩溃，伊恩。
And all my models are pointing
toward a global ecological collapse, Ian.
楼下，下六层。
Downstairs, sublevel six.
那是他们养蝗虫的地方。
That's where they keep
the locusts.
查找标记为 L4 的实验室。
Look for a lab marked L4.
但是等等，我们该如何到达那里呢？
But wait, how are we
gonna get down there?
这看起来很丝滑。我可以碰碰这件衬衫吗？
This looks so silky.
May I touch this blouse, by any chance?
确定。
Sure.
你知道它是什麽吗？别告诉我。这是...
You know what it is?
Don't tell me. This is...
- 你不会知道的。
- ...可持续竹子。
- You won't know it.
- ...sustainable bamboo.
- 它是可持续的竹子。
- 这就是为什麽我说...
- It is sustainable bamboo.
- That's why I said...
- 你怎麽知道的？
- 我就是知道。
- How'd you know?
- I just know.
- 太神奇了。
- 非常惊人。
- It's amazing.
- Very amazing.
我有孜然，肉桂。
I've got cumin, cinnamon.
我有多香果，这不是很受欢迎。
I've got allspice,
which is not very popular.
- 我有五种香料...
- 医生。
- I've got five-spice...
- Doctor.
...如果你喜欢那种感觉。
...if you're into that kind of feel.
嗯，让我们谈谈牛奶。是的。
- Um, and let's talk milks.
- Yeah.
好吧，豆浆，是吗？
Okay, soy milk, yes?
不。刚刚发生了什麽？
- No.
- What just happened?
我们进来了
We're in.
第六级。限制。
Sublevel six. Restricted.
刘易斯，你不听我的。
Lewis, you're not listening to me.
蝗虫的史前DNA使它们比他们应该的更强大。
The locusts' prehistoric DNA has made them
stronger than they should be.
他们疯狂地繁殖，他们没有死。
They're multiplying like crazy
and they're not dying.
- 你不明白其中的哪一部分？
- 我明白了。
- What part of this don't you understand?
- I do understand.
这将是一场全球饥荒。
This is gonna be a global famine.
嘿，嘿，我们不能预测一切。
Hey, hey,
we can't anticipate everything.
我们需要根除我们释放的那些。
We need to eradicate the ones we released.
- 什麽?
- 全部。
- What?
- All of them.
- 不。不。
- 喜欢...
- No. No.
- Like...
- 亨利，我们不想引起恐慌。
- 就象昨天一样。
- Henry, we don't want to cause a panic.
- Like yesterday.
我们想要控制。
We want control.
没有这样的事情。
There's no such thing.
当我们害怕时
When we're afraid,
我们该怎麽办？
what do we do?
我们以前做过什麽？
What have we done before?
我们坚持到底。
We follow through.
我们就是这样做的。
That's what we do.
正确的?
Right?
正确的。
Right.
我们找到了那个女孩。
We found the girl.
她在路上。
She's en route.
- 花了我一大笔钱。
- 什麽?
- Cost me a fortune.
- What?
- 等等，你找到了她？
- 是的，找到了他们俩。
- Wait, you found her?
- Yeah, found them both.
她和小猛禽。
Her and the little raptor.
Blue自己复制了一切，就象你说的一样。
Blue reproduced all on her own,
just like you said.
你太聪明了，亨利。
You're so smart, Henry.
这就是它的工作原理。
That's why this works.
你明白这些生物的价值。
You understand the value
of these creatures.
你总是有。我也是。
You always have.
I do too.
我们不会因为一个，什麽，小副业项目向南走而停止？
We don't stop because of a, what,
little side project went south?
嘿，如果他们把蝗虫追朔到我们身边，
Hey, if they trace the locusts back to us,
他们来是为了恐龙。
they come for the dinosaurs.
你所有的工作，都消失了。
All your work, gone.
数十亿美元的资产，消失了。
Billions of dollars in assets, gone.
钻石，没有人开采它们。
Diamonds with no one to mine them.
你真的认为她是解决方案吗？
You really think
she's the solution?
好。
Okay.
所有涉及女孩的事情都通过我，对吧？
Everything involving the girl
goes through me, right?
她还好吗?
Is she all right?
她最好是。
She better be.
她是这个星球上最有价值的知识产权。
She's the most valuable
intellectual property on the planet.
我说我会给你打电话。
I said I'd call you.
他们降落了吗？
They land yet?
第二架飞机即将进入。
Second plane is incoming.
- 谁说过第二架飞机？
- 我们分开飞行。
- Who said anything about a second plane?
- We flew them separately.
我不会冒任何风险。
I'm not taking any chances.
我们需要在交货前付款。
And we'll need payment before delivery.
我不喜欢上次发生的事情。
I didn't like what happened last time.
好。好吧，完成后给我打电话。
Okay. Okay, just call me when it's done.
你说我要去一个安全的地方。
You said I was going someplace safe.
你是。
You are.
- 走到车上。
- 不。
- Walk to the car.
- No.
这不是一个选择。
It's not a choice.
五十大飞一只小猛禽。
Fifty grand to fly one little raptor.
不错。
Not bad.
女孩怎么了？
What's with the girl?
不是你的问题。
Not your problem.
做生意的乐趣。
Pleasure doing business.
我们准备好了。我们走吧。
We're ready. Let's go.
欧文。
Owen.
嗨，克莱尔。
Hi, Claire.
我以为你会选择一个更安静的工作。
I thought you would've chosen
a quieter line of work.
我试过了。我和表弟开了一家咖啡馆。我持续了三个星期。
I tried. My cousin and I opened a café.
I lasted three weeks.
世界的发展方向，很难把目光移开。
The way the world is headed,
it's hard to look away.
德拉库尔被索约娜·桑托斯聘用
Delacourt was hired by Soyona Santos,
地下恐龙贸易的经纪人。
a broker
in the underground dinosaur trade.
我们没有关于他的货物的情报
We don't have intel on his cargo,
但是一旦他们进行交流，我们就会看到他们对你女孩的了解。
but once they make the exchange,
we'll see what they know about your girl.
你可以听进去，但答应我你不会联系。
You can listen in,
but promise me you will not make contact.
不。
No.
现在有一个很大的恐龙地下市场。
There is a big underground market
for dinosaurs now.
欧洲，中东，北非，这一切都来自这里。
Europe, Middle East, northern Africa,
it all comes through here.
不要看任何人，不要和任何人说话。
Don't look at anyone,
don't talk to anyone.
只是尝试融入。
Just try to blend in.
我没事。
I'm okay.
还在飞向桑托斯，对吧？
Still flying for Santos, huh?
你必须需要钱。
You must need money.
对你来说是什麽？
What's it to you?
我有货。
I've got cargo.
一千公斤的恐龙到巴勒莫。
A thousand kilos of dinosaur
to Palermo.
水龙兽.非常罕见。
Lystrosaurus. Very rare.
我给你两千。
I give you two thousands.
八。
Eight.
他可能很丑，但他有精神。
He may be ugly, but he's got spirit.
- 你打算怎麽处理他？
- 他现在是我的。你在乎什麽？
- What are you gonna do with him?
- He's mine now. What do you care?
是的！来吧，伙计！
Yeah! Come on, man!
是的!
Yes!
你输了？
You lost?
你是美国人。
You're American.
这让我们成为朋友？
And that make us friends?
- 听着，我刚刚来到这里，然后...
- 哦不。
- Listen, I just got here and...
- Oh, no.
这不是邀请。这里。
That was not an invitation. Here.
纪念品。
Souvenir.
回到酒店，你知道，在浴缸里扔一些浴盐。
Go back to the hotel, you know,
throw some bath salts in a bath.
这个地方，不是你的氛围。
This place, not your vibe.
等。
Wait.
- 看。
- 克雷尔。
- Look.
- Claire.
克雷尔。
Claire.
我知道这一定让人感到异国情调
I know this must feel exotic,
但是如果你在这里搞砸了错误的人，你就会消失。
but if you mess with the wrong person
down here, you disappear.
你感觉到我了吗？
You feel me?
祝你好运，好吗？
Good luck, okay?
等。
Wait.
- 等。
- 这是怎麽?
- Wait.
- What is this?
- 我需要你的説明。
- 我不认识你。
- I need your help.
- I don't know you.
- 我在找人。
- 别这样。
- I'm looking for someone.
- Don't do that.
她孤身一人。请。
She is all alone. Please.
- 那个你的女儿？
- 是的。
- That your daughter?
- Yes.
抱歉，我无法参与。
Sorry, I can't get involved.
以为我得到了他。移动目标。
- Think I got him.
- Target on the move.
那是我们和他在一起的卧底特工。
That's our undercover agent
with him.
克雷尔，他正走向地下。
Claire, he's headed underground.
- 你看见他了吗？
- 是的，我有他。
- You see him?
- Yeah, I've got him.
好了,我们走。
All right, let's go.
四队，需要你扫一扫南下。
Team four,
need you to sweep spreading south.
加油!
Come on!
所有单位，采取靶心位置。
All units, take up bull's-eye position.
这是布拉沃一号。
This is Bravo One.
主要目标在视线之内。没有女孩的迹象。
Primary target in sight.
No sign of the girl.
阿尔法团队，站得很清楚。
Alpha team, stand clear.
我的人说猛禽来的时候状况良好。
My people say the raptor arrived
in good condition.
你们这些男孩没有把这个搞砸。
You boys didn't cock this up.
颜色让我惊讶。
Color me amazed.
我确实有另一份工作给你。短促的跳跃，钱的双倍。
I do have another job for you.
Short hop, money's double.
货物是什麽?
What's the cargo?
暴龙.
Atrociraptors.
纯种马。
Thoroughbreds.
受过杀戮训练。
Trained to kill.
- 杀谁？
- 无论他们被告知谁。
- Kill who?
- Whoever they're told.
激光标记目标，它们附着在气味上，直到它死去才停止。
Laser marks the target, they attach
to the scent, don't stop till it's dead.
不可避免。
Inescapable.
那些制造杂交种的白痴都错了。
Those idiots making hybrids
had it all wrong.
你不能设计忠诚。你必须培养它。
You can't engineer loyalty.
You have to nurture it.
50，000飞往利雅德。
50,000 to fly them to Riyadh.
进还是出？
In or out?
她不在这里。
She's not here.
我们要去哪?
Where are we going?
快到了。
Almost there.
- 这就是下降，我们走吧！
- 需要眼睛...
- That's the drop, let's go!
- Need eyes on...
武器倒下！盯着他们！
Weapons down! Eyes on them!
双手在空中！联系达成！
Hands in the air! Contact made!
德拉库尔，现在在地板上！
Delacourt, on the floor now!
在地上！
Get on the ground!
德拉库尔！和他在一起！
Delacourt! Stay with him!
妈的。
Shit.
把那辆卡车从这里拿出来！
Get that truck out of here!
桑托斯去了！
There goes Santos!
该死的，我们失去了德拉库尔。
Damn, we lost Delacourt.
这是布拉沃一号。卡车正在接近地下信道。
This is Bravo One.
Truck is approaching the underpass.
去吧。
Go.
伙计，来吧！滚吧！
Man, come on! Roll it!
女孩，她在哪里？他们把她带到哪里去了？
The girl, where is she?
Where did they take her?
- 拿开!
- 她在哪?
- Get it off!
- Where is she?
我不知道！我们把她交给了桑托斯。
I don't know! We handed her off to Santos.
我不知道在那之后他们把她带到了哪里。
I don't know
where they took her after that.
克雷尔，是桑托斯，白衣女人。
Claire, it's Santos, the woman in white.
我会找到她的。
I'll find her.
- 扩散;传播开。
- 布拉沃团队，注意你的六个。
- Spread out.
- Bravo team, watch your six.
嘿 嘿！嘿！等等！
- Hey, hey! Hey!
- Hold it!
- 让他们出来。
- 什麽?
- Let them out.
- What?
你听到了。
You heard me.
默德。
Merde.
克雷尔，你有她吗？
Claire, do you have her?
- 我们遇到了一些麻烦。
- 何等？
- We had some trouble.
- What kind?
父母，格雷迪和迪林。他们来了。
The parents, Grady and Dearing.
They're here.
- 你能照顾好它吗？
- 不是免费的。
- Can you take care of it?
- Not for free.
好吧，做吧。
Well, do it.
好的好的。听。
Okay, okay. Listen.
哦!
Oh!
不 不 不!
No, no, no!
你不会在人身上使用它。
You don't use it on people.
我女儿呢?
Where's my daughter?
她一开始就不是你的。
She wasn't yours to begin with.
告诉我。
Tell me.
生物合成。
Biosyn.
他们要带她去生物科技。
They're taking her to Biosyn.
你想念她。
You missed her.
她不见了。
She's gone.
拉着我的手。加油。
Take my hand. Come on.
紧紧抓住。
Hold on tight.
什麽?
What?
你还记得我们以前是如何把猛禽弄进卡车的吗？
Do you remember how we used
to get the raptors in the truck?
- 是的。
- Yeah.
- 你起来了。
- 不。
- You're up.
- No.
在最后一刻，潜水滚动。
At the last minute, dive roll.
- 我不潜水滚动。
- 你会没事的。
- I don't dive roll.
- You'll be fine.
我从来没有得到正确的时机。
I never got the timing right.
- 现在?
- 任何分锺。现在任何一分钟。
- Now?
- Any minute. Any minute now.
- 现在?
- 不。
- Now?
- No.
现在!
Now!
是的。是的！
Yeah. Yeah, yeah!
冻结!
Freeze!
我要带我们飞出这里。告诉我你想在哪里被放下。
I'm flying us out of here.
Tell me where you wanna be dropped.
你飞过生物科技吗？
You ever flown to Biosyn?
欧文！他们把她带到了生物科技。
Owen! They took her to Biosyn.
岛的北侧有一个机场。
There's an airfield
on the north side of the island.
去。
Go.
你被捕了。留在原地。
You're under arrest. Stay where you are.
正确的！
Right!
小心！
Heads up!
我们今天制造了很多敌人。我们得走了。
We made a lot of enemies today.
We gotta go.
- 他会在这里。
- 嗯嗯。
- He'll be here.
- Uh-huh.
不合时宜，越来越好。
Out of time, out of time.
他在那儿。
There he is.
- 停车。
- 这不是飞机的工作方式。
- Pull over.
- That's not how planes work.
打开背面。
Open the back.
加油!
Come on!
紧紧抓住!
Hold on tight!
哦。。。
Oh, sh...
还是知道了。
Still got it.
你是。。。你受伤了吗？
Are you... Are you hurt?
- 你没事吧？你受伤了吗？
- 是的。
- Are you okay? You hurt?
- Yeah, yeah.
- 哪里？你在哪里受伤？
- 是的。
- Where? Where are you hurt?
- Yeah.
- 你在哪里受伤？
- 不不。我没事。我没事。
- Where are you hurt?
- No, no. I'm okay. I'm okay.
你没事吧？什麽?
Are you okay? What...
- 骼膊疼得很厉害。是不是流血了？
- 你没事吧?
- Arm hurts pretty bad. Is it bleeding?
- Are you all right?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我是吗？我是吗？
Am I? Am I?
让我想想。
Let me see.
- 是吗...它被切割了吗？
- 不。不。
- Is it... Is it cut?
- No. No.
不,你没事。
No, you're okay.
- 好。
- 你没事。
- Okay.
- You're okay.
凯拉·沃茨。
Kayla Watts.
不客气。
You're welcome.
你看起来不象是为生物科技飞的。
You don't look like you fly for Biosyn.
我将按照你的意思而不是听起来的方式来看待它。
I'm gonna take that the way you meant it
and not the way it sounded.
我为那些得到袋子的人飞，但我们会帮这个忙。
I fly for whoever got a bag,
but we'll call this one a favor.
这些都行不通。他们破产了。
Those don't work. They broke.
我会带你们去生物科技，但我不能保证它不会很危险。
I'll take you all to Biosyn,
but I can't promise it won't be dangerous.
你愿意为了你从未见过的人冒着生命危险吗？
You're willing to risk your life
for people you never met?
您想问问题，还是想乘车？
You wanna ask questions,
or you want a ride?
我们将搭便车。
We'll take the ride.
这是我们的凄息地开发实验室。
So this is
our habitat development lab.
最近有很多令人兴奋的发现。
A lot of exciting discoveries
as of late.
我们以最纯净的形式带回了许多物种，
We've brought back numerous species
in their purest form,
我的意思是完整的，未受破坏的基因组，比如无畏厄兆龙。
and I mean complete, untouched genomes,
like Moros intrepidus.
- 什麽?
- 是的。
- What?
- Yeah.
哇。
Wow.
如何剪接DNA？
What about splicing DNA?
你知道，创造新的物种。
You know, creating new species.
哦，不，萨特勒博士，我们在这里不这样做。
Oh, no, Dr. Sattler,
we don't do that here.
我们喜欢认为自己更进化了。
We like to think we're more evolved.
看起来我们还有一些时间在你的车程之前。
Looks like we still have
some time left before your ride.
呃，你们想自己参观这些设施吗？
Uh, would you guys like to tour
the facilities yourselves?
哦，呃，我的意思是，我们可以。
Oh, uh, I mean, we could.
- 是啊, 为什麽不呢?
- 伟大。
- Yeah, why not?
- Great.
我会在大约30分锺内在三号站的超级高铁上与你们见面。
I'll meet you guys at the hyperloop,
station three in about 30 minutes.
电梯在这个大厅里，而不是那些。
Elevators are down this hall,
not those.
这些将您引导到子级别。
Those lead you
down to the sublevels.
你需要特殊的许可才能到达那里。
You need special clearance
to get down there.
- 哦, 好吧。
- 三十分钟。
- Oh, okay.
- Thirty minutes.
这里。拿着这个。
Here. Take this.
好?
Okay?
是的。
Yep.
我真的很抱歉它必须以这种方式发生。
I'm really sorry
that it had to happen this way.
是的，这就是绑匪所说的。
Yep, that's what kidnappers say.
克雷尔永远不应该把你藏起来。
Claire should never have
hidden you away.
你太重要了，麦茜。
You're way too important, Maisie.
你也带走了她？
You took her too?
是的。
Yeah.
我们需要她帮助我们理解你。
We needed her
to help us understand you.
嘿，贝塔。
Hey, Beta.
你没事吧?
You okay?
你说“贝塔”吗？那是她的名字吗？
Did you say "Beta"? Is that her name?
我把它给了她。
I gave it to her.
Beta非常特别。
Beta is pretty special.
你知道，当我们制作蓝色时，
You know, when we made Blue,
我们使用监测蜥蜴的DNA来填补她基因组中的空白。
we used monitor lizard DNA
to fill in the gaps in her genome.
巨蜥可以在没有配偶的情况下繁殖。
Monitor lizards can reproduce
without a mate.
所以贝塔和蓝色在基因上是相同的
So Beta and Blue
are genetically identical,
这就是他们与你和...
and that's what they have
in common with you and...
夏 洛特。
Charlotte.
你对夏洛特了解多少？
What do you know about Charlotte?
她死了
She died.
很久以前
A long time ago.
这让我爷爷心碎了。
It broke my grandpa's heart.
所以他创造了我。
So he made me.
不，麦茜。实际上，他没有。
No, Maisie. Actually, he didn't.
夏洛特创造了你。
Charlotte made you.
我很高兴每个人都能看到我们在这里所做的一切。
I'm so excited for everyone to see
what we've been doing here.
有新的技术正在被制造出来，新的科学，就象，几乎每天都有。
There's new technology being made,
new science, like, every day almost.
在市中心真是太好了...其中心。
And it's great to be in the center of...
Center of that.
夏洛特和我们所有人一起住在B站，直到暴风雨。
Charlotte lived on Site B
with all of us till the storm.
她喜欢恐龙。
She loved dinosaurs.
夏洛特，小心。是的，我会的。
- Charlotte, be careful.
- Yeah, I will.
她在科学家的周围长大。
She grew up around scientists.
最终...
And eventually...
她自己也成了一个。
she became one herself.
今天早上，一只蝴蝶飞了我的办公室。
A butterfly flew
info my office this morning.
他们说小事有巨大的影响，我全心全意地同意。
They say tiny things have huge impacts,
and I agree wholeheartedly.
她很出色
She was brilliant.
对于我所有与生物的工作，翅膀拍打...
For all my work with creatures,
wings flapping...
以我永远不会的方式。
In ways that I'll never be.
在身分的形而上学中，复制品真的能是原件吗？
In the metaphysics of identity,
can a replica truly be the original?
如果这是可能的，那麽是什麽让它如此？
And if it's possible, what makes it so?
我丢了笔。
I've lost my pen.
是我吗？
Is that me?
是的。
Yeah.
就象布鲁一样，夏洛特能够独自生一个孩子。
Just like Blue, Charlotte was able
to have a child all by herself.
她用自己的DNA创造了你。
She created you with her own DNA.
所以我确实有一个母亲。
So I do have a mother.
你爷爷不想让任何人知道真相。
Your grandfather didn't want
anyone to know the truth.
他在保护她，还有你。
He was protecting her, and you.
我们是一样的吗？
And we're the same?
你是.
You were.
当你还是个婴儿的时候，夏洛特开始出现遗传性疾病的症状。
When you were a baby, Charlotte started
to show symptoms of a genetic disorder.
她就是这样死的。
That's how she died.
直到你出生後，她才知道她有它。
She didn't know she had it
until after you were born.
- 我也有吗？
- 不。
- Do I have it too?
- No.
她改变了你的DNA。
She changed your DNA.
她改变了你身体的每一个细胞，以根除这种疾病。
She altered every cell in your body
to eradicate this disease.
地球上没有人知道如何做到这一点。
No one on earth has ever known
how to do that.
她修好了我。
She fixed me.
夏洛特的发现现在是你的一部分。
Charlotte's discovery
is a part of you now.
你的DNA可以改变世界。
Your DNA could change the world.
我必须知道她是怎麽做到的，但我就是无法复制她的作品。
And I have to know how she did it,
but I just can't replicate her work.
如果我能研究你和贝塔，他们的DNA从未改变过，我可以......
If I could just study you and Beta,
whose DNA was never changed, I could...
修复我犯的一个可怕的错误。
fix a terrible mistake that I've made.
什麽样的错误？
What kind of mistake?
第六级。限制。
Sublevel six. Restricted.
谢谢你的来。
Thanks for coming.
玛律科姆说的是哪个实验室？L4.
- Which lab did Malcolm say?
- L4.
就是这样。
This is it.
好。进去，拿到样品，然后出去。
Okay. Get in,
get the sample and get out.
并缓慢移动。
And move slow.
它们可以在最轻微的干扰下蜂拥而至。
They can swarm
at the slightest disturbance.
直翅目。
Orthoptera.
两周。
Two weeks.
完全成熟。这个。
Fully mature. This one.
准备？容易。
Ready? Easy.
好。去。
Okay. Go.
什麽?
What?
去拿吧
Go get it.
有必要吗？
Is that necessary?
为何-你认为会发生什麽？
Wh-What did you think was gonna happen?
我必须取一个样本。我们需要具体的证据。就是这样。
I have to take a sample.
We need concrete evidence. This is it.
艾伦，你说没有时间。你能得到它吗？
Alan, you said there was no time.
Can you get it?
当然，我可以得到它。
Of course I can get it.
好。容易。
Okay. Easy.
注意它的腿。
Watch its legs.
呸。是的。
Ugh. Yech.
来吧。
Here we go.
它们是它们之间的细胞信号传导。这不好，艾莉。
They're cell signaling between them.
This is not good, Ellie.
我差点就明白了。
I almost got it.
亨利，如果你把我们俩都牵连起来，她怎麽仍然是一笔资产呢？
How does she remain an asset, Henry,
if you're incriminating both of us
通过在电脑上显示她的机密内容？
by showing her classified things
on the computer?
夏洛特·洛克伍德相信侏罗纪公园使用的方法
Charlotte Lockwood believed
the methods used at Jurassic Park
可以治愈疾病。
could cure disease.
她是对的。
She was right.
用改变的DNA填补了Maisie基因组中的空白
Having filled the gaps
in Maisie's genome with altered DNA,
她使用病原体将修复后的串行传递到每个细胞。
she used a pathogen to deliver
the repaired sequence to every cell.
如果我能重新利用她的所作所为，我就能改变蝗虫的DNA
If I can repurpose what she did,
I could change the locust DNA,
在一代人的时间雷根除它们。
eradicating them in a single generation.
麦茜和小猛禽将提供缺失的数据。
Maisie and the baby raptor
will provide the missing data.
嘿，你想离开这里吗？
Hey, do you wanna get out of here?
什麽。。。
What the...
明白了。
Got it.
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
它们无处不在！帮帮我！
They're everywhere! Help me!
天啊！不！
Oh, God! No!
哦,我的上帝!哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
梅西
Maisie.
资产遏制违槼。
Asset containment breach.
请留在您的车站。
Please remain at your stations.
资产遏制违槼。请留在您的车站。
Asset containment breach.
Please remain at your stations.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
- 天啊。我看不见！
- 关键在哪里？
- Oh, God. I can't see!
- Where's the key?
天啊!
Oh, God!
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的。你？
Yeah. You?
是的。
Yeah.
哦。
Oh.
你是艾莉·萨特勒博士和艾伦·格兰特。
You're Dr. Ellie Sattler and Alan Grant.
你在侏罗纪公园。
You were at Jurassic Park.
你在这里干什麽?
What are you doing here?
什麽？什麽。。。
What? What...
你在这里干什麽?
What are you doing here?
我是麦茜洛克伍德。
I'm Maisie Lockwood.
呃，嘿，我们没有，呃...
Uh, hey, we don't, uh...
我们不是...我们不为生物科技工作。
We're not...
We don't work for Biosyn.
我可以说
I can tell.
- 我们得离开这里
- 是的，我们应该走了。
- We gotta get out of here.
- Yeah, we should go.
好。仔细地。我们找到你的女孩，然后走。
Okay. In and out.
We find your girl and go.
塔，这是N141。要求上岸进行货物运输。多。
Tower, this is N141. Request to land
for freight delivery. Over.
N141，阴性。
N141, negative.
我们被告知您携带未经授权的乘客。多。
We've been advised you're carrying
unauthorized passengers. Over.
复制它，塔。请注意，货件易腐烂。
Copy that, Tower.
Be advised shipment is perishable.
我们需要立即清除。这是紧急情况。多。
We need immediate clearance.
It's an emergency. Over.
没有...不。
There isn't... No.
阴性。返回到原点。
Negative.
Return to point of origin.
你似乎要分手了。你听到我站在你这边了吗？
You seem to be breaking up.
Are you hearing me on your side?
可能需要检查系统。
May need to check systems.
不错的尝试，凯拉。他们会打倒你的鸟。
Nice try, Kayla.
They will down your bird.
你是谁？这是丹妮丝吗？
Who is this?
Is this Denise?
你不希望我开始泄露秘密，丹妮丝。你还记得杜布罗夫尼克。
You do not want me to start spilling
secrets, Denise. You remember Dubrovnik.
她...
She's...
不同的邓尼斯，在帐户中。
Different Denise, in accounts.
和桑托斯谈过。这是女孩的父母。
Talked to Santos.
It's the girl's parents.
让我们关闭广告。
Let's shut off the ADS.
是否确定?
Are you sure?
嗯嗯。
Uh-huh.
什麽?
What's that?
呃...
Uh...
就是这样，呃...这就是空中威慑系统。
That's the, uh...
That's the Aerial Deterrent System.
- 远离空气中的生命。
- 为什麽会闪铄？
- Keeps the airborne life away.
- Why is it blinking?
塔里的死屁股丹妮丝刚刚把它关掉了。
Dead ass Denise in the tower
just turned it off.
我们现在必须离开这个空域。
We gotta get out of this airspace
right now.
- 那是另一架飞机，对吧？
- 不完全是。
- That's another plane, right?
- Not exactly.
这是...风神翼龙属.
- Is that a...
- Quetzalcoatlus.
白垩纪晚期，应该住在那里。
Late Cretaceous,
should have stayed there.
好。好。
Okay. Okay.
这很酷。我们很好。不见了。
It's cool. We're good. It's gone.
这架飞机要坠毁了！
This plane is going down!
如果您要弹出，则需要立即运行此操作！
If you're gonna eject,
you need to do it now!
- 我只有一把椅子，她就在里面。
- 你没有降落伞吗？
- I only got one chair, and she's in it.
- You don't have parachutes?
我没想到公司！
I wasn't expecting company!
克雷尔！我们必须把你从这架飞机上下来。
Claire! We gotta get you off this plane.
什麽?
What?
降落伞将自动打开。
The parachute is gonna open automatically.
如果没有，你拉动这个杠杆。你理解我吗？
If it doesn't, you pull this lever.
Do you understand me?
克雷尔！如果它没有自动打开，
Claire!
If it doesn't open automatically,
你要把这个杠杆拉到你身后。好？
you're gonna pull
this lever behind you. Okay?
一万英尺！
Ten thousand feet!
嘿，你是那个必须去找她的人。
Hey, you're the one
who's gotta go to get to her.
你是她的妈妈。你是她唯一的镜头。
You're her mom.
You're her only shot.
再见了
I'll see you again.
我爱你。
I love you.
计划是什麽?
What's the plan?
无论发生什麽。这就是计划。
Whatever happens. That's the plan.
- 三。
- 这边。
- Three.
- This way.
艾伦，我们需要代码。让我们试试这个东西。
- Alan, we need the code.
- Let's try this thing.
是的。
Yeah.
趴下。
Get down.
- 感谢上帝，这是你！
- 我知道。
- Thank God it's you!
- I know.
- 这个地方是迷宫。
- 好你来了。
- This place is a maze.
- Good you're here.
我们太困惑了。我以为我们迷路了。
We were so confused.
I thought we were lost.
然后你说第三站。我当时想，在这里...
Then you said station three.
And I was like, here...
你有样品吗？
Do you have the sample?
- 什麽?
- 你在谈论什麽?
- What?
- What are you talking about?
DNA样本。你有吗？
The DNA sample. Do you have it?
生物合成负责蝗虫流行。
Biosyn's responsible
for the locust epidemic.
道奇森掩盖了它。你是对的。
Dodgson's covering it up.
You were right.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you.
你有吗？
Do you have it?
是的。
Yeah.
好。
Good.
这个吊舱将带您到机场。
This pod will take you
to the airfield.
我们有一架飞机准备飞行。
We have a plane ready to fly.
- 伊恩跟你说过六足盟友？
- 不。
- Ian told you about Hexapod Allies?
- No.
我告诉他。
I told him.
什麽?
What?
- 好。你们得走了。
- 等。
- Okay. You guys gotta go.
- Wait.
梅西
Maisie.
麦茜·洛克伍德。
Maisie Lockwood.
去。
Go.
好。
Okay.
那是我的孩子。
That was my baby.
好的。
Okay, okay.
你在哪里学过飞行？
Where'd you learn to fly?
呃，空军。我妈妈那边的遗产。
Uh, Air Force.
Legacy on my mama's side.
是的。我是海军。
Yeah. I'm Navy.
好吧，那麽你最终是如何做到这一点的呢？
Okay, so how'd you end up doing this?
我是一个合法的合同飞行员
I was a legit contract pilot
for a grip,
但它并没有支付足够的钱来在这里寄钱回家。
but it didn't exactly pay enough
to be out here sending money home.
所以我打了几个联系人，以获得更有利可图的阴暗狗屎。
So I hit up a few contacts
for the more lucrative shady shit.
老实说，我可能已经完成了这项工作。
Honestly, I might be done
with this line of work.
这就是你帮助我们的原因吗？
Is that why you're helping us?
当他们把你的女孩交给生物科技时，我就在那里。
I was there
when they handed your girl off to Biosyn.
我本来可以说些什麽，但我没有。
I could have said something, but I didn't.
当我看到她的照片时...
And when I saw her picture...
什麽都不做是不够的。
It isn't enough to do nothing.
谢谢。
Thank you.
不。
No.
Nope.
真是个混蛋。
What an asshole.
你很好?
You good?
是的。是的。是的，我一点也不动摇。你？
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm not shook at all. You?
不。不不。
Nah. Nah, no.
弹射座椅信标。我们会找到她的。
Ejection seat beacon.
We'll find her.
好的。
Okay, okay.
你真的爱她，对吧？
You really love her, huh?
是的。
Yeah.
我明白了。
I get it.
我也喜欢红头发。
I like redheads too.
什麽？神。
What? God.
- 那是谁?
- 这是格兰特和萨特勒。
- Who is that?
- It's Grant and Sattler.
- 这是活的吗？
- 十二分钟前。
- Is this live?
- Twelve minutes ago.
我们正在跟踪逃逸的资产。我的人错过了它。
We were tracking the escaped asset.
My guys missed it.
他们偷走了DNA样本。
They stole a DNA sample.
他们是怎麽进入那里的？
How'd they get in there?
他们使用了访问密钥。洋基白清除。
They used an access key.
Yankee White clearance.
我们的一台摄象机看到伊恩·玛律科姆 在萨特勒的口袋里放了一些东西。
One of our cameras saw Ian Malcolm
put something in Sattler's pocket.
好吧。我想见见他。
All right.
I want to see him.
把拉姆齐也带到这里来，对吧？
And get Ramsay up here too,
will you?
- 他们现在在哪里？
- 在去机场的路上。
- Where are they now?
- On the way to the airfield.
他们按时赶上了超级高铁。
They caught the hyperloop
right on schedule.
你好吗?
How are you?
你没事吧?
You all right?
不是真的，不是。
Not really, no.
嘿。
Hey.
我，呃，认识妈。
I, uh, knew your mom.
你有吗?
You did?
嗯嗯。
Mm-hmm.
是的，哈蒙德死后几年
Yeah, a few years
after Hammond died,
她来我大学讲课
she came to my university to lecture,
我们成了好朋友。
and we became good friends.
她是什麽样的人？
What was she like?
辉煌。
Brilliant.
比其他人领先几光年。
Light-years ahead
of everybody else.
她有良知。
And she had a conscience.
当他们外出建造主题公园时
While they were out
building theme parks,
好吧，她决心证明遗传力量可以挽救生命。
well, she was determined to prove
that genetic power could save lives.
我是她的实验。
And I was her experiment.
不。
No.
她最想要一个孩子。
She wanted a child more than anything.
但她希望你拥有她不能拥有的东西。
But she wanted you to have
what she couldn't.
充实的生活。
A full life.
我认识她的时间不长，
I didn't know her long,
但我知道她非常爱你。
but I know she loved you very much.
发生了什麽事情?
What's happening?
这一定是旧的琥珀矿。
This must be the old amber mines.
我们在山里。
We're inside the mountain.
他们在建造这些隧道时必须设置门。
They must've made access doors
when they built these tunnels.
准备好了吗?
You ready?
我很好。
I'm good.
不，这是不合理的。
No, that's not reasonable.
你想进入黑暗的隧道。
You want to go into the dark tunnel.
我想留在防弹管里。
I want to stay in the bulletproof tube.
谁在不讲道理？
Who's being unreasonable?
但防弹管没有门。
But the bulletproof tube has no door.
看，呃...
Look, uh...
我知道你的感受。它。。。这太可怕了。是的。
I know how you feel.
It's... It's scary. It is.
但相信我，向前迈进总比保持静止要好。
But trust me, moving forward
is better than staying still.
而萨特勒博士在这里是个好人，处于紧张状态
And Dr. Sattler here is
a good person in a tight spot,
这是一个紧张的地方。
and this is a tight spot.
所以，你来了？
So, you coming?
好吧。
All right.
嘿，我听到了警报。一切都好吗？
Hey, I heard the alarm.
Everything all right?
是的。不不。没有什麽我们不能，呃，处理。听。。。
Yeah. No, no.
Nothing we can't, uh, handle. Listen...
- 你响了吗？
- 哦,很好。
- You rang?
- Oh, good.
玛律科姆博士，你是...
Dr. Malcolm, you are...
- 解雇。
- 什麽?
- fired.
- What?
这是一场如此舒适的演出。
It was such a cushy gig.
如果您仍然拥有访问密钥，则可以将其提供给安全性。
You can give your access key to security
if you still have it.
其中一个超级高铁吊舱刚刚在琥珀矿井中关闭。
One of the hyperloop pods
just shut down in the amber mines.
什麽?
What?
哇。这一天。
Wow. This day.
呃，这...我们是哪个吊舱...
Uh, which... Which pod are we...
有吗，嗯...
Are there, um...
矿井里的恐龙？
dinosaurs in the mines?
到处都是恐龙。
There are dinosaurs everywhere.
从技术上讲，鸟类是恐龙，至少从g遗传学上讲。
Technically, birds are dinosaurs,
g-genetically speaking at least.
好。刘易斯，格兰特和萨特勒就在这个豆荚里。
Okay.
Lewis, Grant and Sattler are in this pod.
- 我们需要尽快派出一个安全团队。
- 当然可以，拉姆齐。谢谢。
- We need to send a security team ASAP.
- Absolutely, Ramsay. Thank you.
不过，让我们都呆在我们的车道上。我们可以照顾它。
Let's all just stay in our lanes though.
We can take care of it.
谢谢你 医生。
Thank you, Doctor.
就是这样，对吧？这里没什麽可看的吗？
That's it, huh?
Nothing else to see here?
呃，我不确定我现在是否欣赏你的语气。
Uh, I'm not sure
I admire your tone right now.
- 你需要离开。
- 是的,我愿意。
- You need to leave.
- Yeah, I do.
但首先，我欠所有这些人一个道歉。
But first,
I owe all these folks an apology.
我认为，通过把我的声望借给这个关节
I think that by lending my cachet
to this joint,
我可能会让生物科技看起来好象没有腐烂到核心。
I might've made it seem
as if Biosyn wasn't rotten to the core.
够了，伊恩。
That's enough, Ian.
看，这是他们如何得到你。
See, here's how they get you.
他们在短时间内为您提供如此多的促销活动
They give you so many promotions
in a short period of time
它打击了你的批判性思维能力。
that it bludgeons your capacity
for critical thinking.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
然后有一些你没有打开的门，你忽略的东西。
Then there are doors that you don't open,
things that you ignore.
但主要是，他正在利用你对这些的魅力。
But mainly, he's exploiting
your enchantment with these.
这里是否有实际问题，或者您只是...
Is there an actual concern here,
or are you just...
你正在朝着我们物种的灭绝冲刺，你不在乎。
You're racing toward the extinction
of our species, and you don't care.
你确切地知道你在做什麽，但你不会停止。
You know exactly what you're doing,
but you won't stop.
你不能。
You can't.
我以为你可能不一样，但你和其他人一样。
I thought you might be different,
but you're just like everyone else.
你看到你想看到的东西。
You see what you want to see.
你想象不受控制的贪婪，所以这就是你发现的。
You imagine unchecked avarice,
so that's what you find.
你想象，什麽，一个邪恶的，未绑定的普罗米修斯
You envision, what,
an evil, unbound Prometheus,
- 这就是我对你的看法？
- 普罗米修斯被吓坏了。
- so that's what I am to you?
- Prometheus got gored.
你也会，你这个贪婪的老鼠混蛋。
So will you, you rapacious rat bastard.
拉姆齐，你会帮助玛律科姆博士收拾他的东西吗？
Ramsay, will you help Dr. Malcolm
gather his things?
他的房间，然后到机场。就是这样。
His room, and then to the airfield.
That's it.
道奇森。
Dodgson.
异特龙？
Allosaurus?
巨龙。
Giganotosaurus.
已知最大的陆生食肉动物。
Largest known terrestrial carnivore.
他把两个顶级捕食者放在一个山谷里。
He put two apex predators in one valley.
很快，就只有一个了。
Pretty soon there's only gonna be one.
你感觉到了吗？
Did you feel that?
那是气流。
That's an air current.
必须是一个开放的前方。
Must be an opening up ahead.
你认为这个矿有多少年的历史了？
How old is this mine,
do you think?
呼吸吧。
Just breathe.
没有人惊慌失措。只要小心蝙蝠。
Nobody panic.
Just watch out for bats.
- 谁对蝙蝠说过什麽？
- 我讨厌蝙蝠。
- Who said anything about bats?
- I hate bats.
嗯，可能没有蝙蝠。没有落石。
Well, there's probably no bats.
No falling rocks.
只是有毒气体，脱水，体温过低的可能性。
Just a possibility of toxic gas,
dehydration, hypothermia.
只是可能性，没有什麽确定的。
Just possibilities, nothing for certain.
我应该把你留在原地。我为什麽要把你带进来？
I should've left you where you were.
Why did I bring you into this?
- 你在你的元素中很快乐。
- 什麽？什麽？艾莉。
- You were happy in your element.
- What? What? Ellie.
什麽?
What?
我不高兴。
I wasn't happy.
你不是吗？
You weren't?
你们有孩子吗？什麽？
- Do you guys have kids?
- What?
呃。。。不。我-我做。两个。
Uh... no. I-I do. Two.
但不是和他在一起吗？
But not with him?
呃...不。
Uh... no.
不，只是老朋友。
No, just old friends.
呃，只是老朋友。
Uh, just old friends.
真?
Really?
不久之后，保安人员就会知道你已经离开了。
Won't be long
before security knows you're gone.
地图。这看起来象一张旧地图。您没有新地图？
A map. That looks like an old map.
You don't have a new map?
在矿井的东北角有一个入口。
There's an access gate
at the northeast corner of the mine.
- 如果你的朋友成功了...
- 如果？
- If your friends make it out...
- If?
- 当他们成功时。
- 是的,先生。
- When they make it out.
- Yes, sir.
这就是他们将要去的地方。
That's where they'll be.
这些道路是受保护的，对吧？
These roads are protected, right?
呃，是的，我会开得快。
Uh, yeah, I'd drive fast.
你干的很好。
You did good.
是的。好吧，实际上，这是一场彻底的灾难，但谢谢。
Yeah. Well, actually,
it's a complete disaster, but thanks.
还没有。
Not yet.
刘易斯?
Lewis?
什麽？你在这里做什麽？
What? What are you doing down here?
其实不然。这很好。
Actually, no. This is good.
你派了一支救援队进入矿井，寻找格兰特和萨特勒？
You sent a rescue team
into the mines for Grant and Sattler?
是的。什麽？好。答案是肯定的。是的。
Yeah. What? Okay. Of course. Yeah.
- 是否正在删除研究档？
- 呃，我们是。是的。
- Are you deleting research files?
- Uh, we are. Yes.
你和我必须保护我们建造的东西，对吧？
You and I got to protect
what we've built, right?
你认为他们不想把手伸到这里来吗？
You think they wouldn't love
to get their hands in here?
拿走我花了几十年时间收集的所有资源。
Take all the resources
I've spent decades collecting.
只是因为，什麽？
Just because, what?
我们打了一个糟糕的电话？它发生了。
We made a bad call? It happens.
七。
Seven.
六足盟友。
Hexapod Allies.
什麽？哦。
What? Oh.
好。人们知道什麽？
Okay. What do people know?
蝗虫旨在将基因改造传播给农作物。
The locusts were designed to spread
genetic modifications to crops.
防止干旱，霜冻，疾病。一个突破。
Protection against droughts,
frost, disease. A breakthrough.
- 该死的，没错。
- 是的。只是它不起作用。
- Goddamn right it was.
- Yeah. Only it didn't work.
你确保他们不能吃生物合成种子，所以他们吃其他所有东西。
You ensured they can't eat Biosyn seed,
so they're eating everything else.
我没有看到来。我们有一个解决方案。
Which I did not see coming.
We have a solution.
- 独立农民起初遭受了痛苦。
- 亨利在上面。
- Independent farmers suffered at first.
- Henry's on it.
没有人在乎。现在，世界粮食供应正濒临崩溃。
Nobody cared much. Now the world's
food supply is verging on collapse.
找到女孩，改变蝗虫的DNA。
Find the girl, change the locusts' DNA.
- 这条小径会回到你身边。
- 我们解决问题。
- The trail's gonna lead back to you.
- We solve the problem.
拉姆齐，谢谢你。
Ramsay, thank you.
在下一个新闻周期中消失，就象其他一切一样。事实并非如此。
Disappears in the next news cycle,
just like everything else. This is not it.
81C1.
或者你可以承担责任。
Or you could accept responsibility.
与世界分享您的研究成果。
Share your research with the world.
是的。
Yep.
你知道，我曾经28岁。我明白了。
You know, I was 28 once. I get it.
你环顾四周，你...
You look around, you...
意识到你被不公正和残酷所包围，你想改变它。
realize you're surrounded by injustice
and cruelty and you wanna change it.
是的。
Yep.
然后你长大了
And then you grow up,
有人让你负责
somebody puts you in charge,
你看到没有改变它。
and you see that there is no changing it.
这是叽叽喳喳喳或被
It's chomp or be chomped.
- 你要去哪里？
- 哦。
- Where are you going with that?
- Oh.
我们不为自己的错误道歉。我们擦除它们。
We don't apologize for our mistakes.
We erase them.
留在手机上。我可能需要你。
Stay on your phone. I may need you.
注意你自己。
Watch yourself.
- 艾莉?
- 是的。
- Ellie?
- Yeah.
那是什麽?
What was that?
小心。
Be careful.
哦，我的上帝。你没事吧？
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
忘掉帽子吧！
Forget the hat!
加油!
Come on!
走,走,走!
Go, go, go!
走,走,走,走,走!
Go, go, go, go, go!
没有按钮。
There's no button.
这是一辆车。
It's a car.
- 哦，我的上帝。伊恩！
- 伊恩，过来！
- Oh, my God. Ian!
- Ian, over here!
- 説明!
- 请!
- Help!
- Please!
- 开门!
- 请帮帮我们!
- Open the gate!
- Please help us!
- 您知道代码吗？
- 我不知道会有代码。
- Do you know the code?
- I didn't know there was gonna be a code.
我不知道会有代码。
I didn't know there was gonna be a code.
哦,我的上帝!哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
刹车！踩刹车！
The brake!
Pull the brake!
有10，000种可能性。
There are 10,000 possibilities.
把你的腿推到它上面！
Push your legs against it!
- 1984.
- 来吧，伊恩！
- Come on, Ian!
踢起来反对它！快 点！
- Kick up against it!
- Hurry!
迈尔斯·大卫斯的生日，0526。
Miles Davis's birthday, 0526.
伊恩！请。请。
- Ian!
- Please. Please.
- 做点什麽!
- 我们不会成功。
- Do something!
- We're not gonna make it.
让我们...让我们都努力保持积极的态度。
Let's... Let's all try to stay positive.
- 请!
- 我知道。我知道。我知道！
- Please!
- I know. I know. I know!
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
你知道什麽？它实际上奏效了。
What do you know?
It actually worked.
- 伊恩，这是麦茜。
- 嗨，麦茜。
- Ian, this is Maisie.
- Hi, Maisie.
我们得到了DNA。
We got the DNA.
- 我们需要走出这个山谷。
- 是的。
- We need to get out of this valley.
- Yeah.
- 加油。加油。
- 我们走吧。我们走吧。
- Come on. Come on.
- Let's go. Let's go.
加油。加油。
Come on. Come on.
继续。获取！
Go on. Get!
呸。
Yuck.
嘿。
Hey.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
我以为你死了。
I thought you were dead.
他们甚至吃什麽？
What do they even eat?
我们最好进去。
We better get inside.
继续。
Go ahead.
安全壳室受损。
Containment chamber compromised.
锁上了。
It's locked.
需要一些重物，一些尖锐的东西，或者两者兼而有之。
Gonna need something heavy,
something sharp, or both.
那不可能是对的。
That can't be right.
- 那是。。。
- 哦不。
- Is that...
- Oh, no.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
他正在焚烧证据。
He's burning the evidence.
- 哦，我的上帝。哦，我的上帝！哦，我的...
- 那是香蕉。
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God! Oh, my...
- That's bananas.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
我。。。我知道这似乎很不稳定，但是...
I... I know that
this may seem precarious, but...
不，我们摇摇欲坠。
No, we're teetering.
难道我们不应该都向左倾斜吗？
Shouldn't we all lean
to the left or something?
这是一个非常有建设性的...谢谢你，麦茜。
That's a very constructive...
Thank you, Maisie.
是的。
Yeah.
慢。慢。
Slow. Slow.
慢。
Slow.
耶。
Yay.
- 我们很好。看到了这个吗？
- 嗯嗯。
- We're fine. See this?
- Mm-hmm.
- 这很好。
- 嗯嗯。
- This is fine.
- Mm-hmm.
艾伦？
Alan?
艾伦！
Alan!
大家好吗？
How is everybody?
是我的父母。
It's my parents.
説明!
Help!
説明！听。
- Help!
- Listen.
説明!
Help!
天啊。
Oh, God.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
你没事。
You're okay.
你是来抓我的。你实际上...你是来抓我的。
You came to get me. You actually...
You came to get me.
当然，我们做到了，亲爱的。
Of course we did, sweetheart.
- 嘿。
- 答案是肯定的。
- Hey.
- Of course.
我记得你。
I remember you.
也要记住你。
Remember you too.
他们帮我逃脱了。
They helped me escape.
是的?
Yeah?
你没事吧?
You okay?
- 谢谢。
- 是的。
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
我们得走了。
We gotta go.
将不得不打破一扇窗户才能进入那个东西。
Gonna have to break a window
to get inside that thing.
希望没有人恐高。
Hope nobody is afraid of heights.
- 别动。
- Don't move.
什麽?
What is that?
巨龙。
Giganotosaurus.
世界上最大的食肉动物。
Biggest carnivore the world has ever seen.
麦茜，麦茜。看着我。看着我。
Maisie, Maisie.
Look at me. Look at me.
去。
Go.
- 走,走,走。
- 加油!
- Go, go, go.
- Come on!
不!不 不。
No! No, no, no.
- 喧嚣！
- 我要死了！
- Hustle!
- I'm gonna die!
- 爬！爬吧，孩子！
- 不!
- Climb! Climb, kid!
- No!
你不是。不，你不是。你没事。
You're not. No, you're not.
You're okay.
走,走,走。
Go, go, go.
加油。
Come on.
嘿!
Hey!
哦，是的。过来这里。
Oh, yeah. Come here.
帮我打开它。
Help me open it.
我抓到你了
I got ya.
走,走,走。
Go, go, go.
走,走,走!
Go, go, go!
运行!
Run!
看？没那麽糟糕。
See? Not so bad.
加油。
Come on.
- 欧文！
- 克雷尔!
- Owen!
- Claire!
调用疏散。我们需要把动物带进去。
Call an evacuation.
We need to bring the animals inside.
槼定很清楚，如果发生二级...
The regulations are clear
that in the event of a level two...
嘘!
Shh!
杰弗里。
Jeffrey.
上帝。。。
God...
该死!
Damn it!
只是。。。
Just...
就这麽称呼它吧。
Just call it.
注意，注意。这是一个立即疏散命令。
Attention, attention.
This is an immediate evacuation order.
远程放牧系统现已启动。
Remote herding system
is now active.
所有活资产都在进入紧急遏制状态。
All living assets en route
to emergency containment.
我无法抓住任何人，因为一切都着火了。
I can't get hold of anybody
since everything is on fire.
- 萨特勒博士，拿点水来。
- 哦 谢谢。
- Dr. Sattler, get some water.
- Oh, thanks.
格兰特博士？给你。
Dr. Grant?
Here you are.
我是欧文·格雷迪。大风扇。我读了你的书。
I'm Owen Grady.
Big fan. I read your book.
好吧，在磁带上书。
Well, book on tape.
欧文·格雷迪。欧文·格雷迪。是的，我知道你是谁。
Owen Grady. Owen Grady.
Yeah, I know who you are.
你们训练猛禽。
You trained raptors.
我试过了。是的。
I tried. Yeah.
- 你好吗?
- 这里的那个。
- How you doing?
- The one here.
你在侏罗纪世界。
You were at Jurassic World.
侏罗纪世界？不是粉丝。嗯嗯嗯。
Jurassic World? Not a fan.
Mm-mmm.
好。所以，我们很好找到一条出路？
Okay.
So, we good to find a way out of here?
- 是的。
- 让我们得到它。
- Yep.
- Let's get it.
在主建筑群里有一架直升机。
There's a helicopter
out in the main complex.
我们重新打开ADS，我们回家。
We turn the ADS back on, we go home.
等。什麽是广告？空中威慑系统。
- Wait. What's an ADS?
- Aerial Deterrent System.
你知道的？对于翼手龙和狗屎。
You know?
For the pterodactyls and shit.
让他们远离直升机。
Keeps them away from the helicopters.
那麽，我们如何重新打开它呢？
Well, how do we turn it back on?
看起来所有的系统都运行到控制室
It looks like all the systems
run through to the control room,
位于三楼。
which is on the third floor.
这些前哨站都连接在地下。
These outposts
are all connected underground.
好吧。容易，兰博。
All right. Easy, Rambo.
所以你在猛禽围栏工作，对吧？
So you worked
in the raptor pen, huh?
是的。
Yeah.
哇。然后呢？
Wow. And what happens?
你只是告诉他们该做什麽，他们遵守了吗？或。。。
Do you just tell them what to do
and they comply? Or...
嗯，这是一种基于相互尊重的人与动物的纽带。
Well, it's a human-animal bond
based on mutual respect.
嗯嗯。
Mm-hmm.
我曾经养过一只狗。
I had a dog once.
我的腿哼了起来，我的胫骨上有一根老茧。
Humped my leg so much
I got a callus on my shinbone.
这是一个真实的故事。
That's a true story.
天啊。嘿。好。
Oh, God. Hey. Good.
这是我在想的。我们又开始了。
Here's what I'm thinking.
We get started again.
你和我。我可以得到钱。
You and me.
I can get money.
是的。如今，钱很便宜。
Yeah. Money's cheap these days.
Wh-怎么了？不要看起来那麽担心。有...
Wh-What's the matter?
Don't look so worried. There's...
一切都有机会。E-即使是这个。你会学到这一点。
There's opportunity in everything.
E-Even this. You'll learn that.
我一直在想，也许你现在会占据更多的领先优势。好？
I've been thinking,
maybe you take more of a lead now. Okay?
你已经准备好了，我想。
You're ready, I think.
在这里，采取...
Here, take...
你到底怎么了？
What the hell
is the matter with you?
是你。
It was you.
你告诉玛律科姆这个项目。你...
You told Malcolm
about the program. Y-You...
你把整个事情都设置好了。你设置了我。
You set this whole thing up.
You set me up.
我给了你每一个我没有的机会。我。。。
I gave you every opportunity
I did not have. I...
我们有一个理解，拉姆齐。你不会打破它。
We have an understanding, Ramsay.
And you do not break that.
我不会打破这个。
I would not break this.
我不是你。
I'm not you.
哦哦。
Uh-oh.
这是非常糟糕的。
This is very bad.
这与我们在公园中使用的系统相同。
This is the same system
we used at the park.
伟大。所以我们可以打开这个东西，然后我们都离开这里？
Great. So we can turn on the thing
and then we all get out of here?
我看看。广告。。。
Let's see. ADS...
这是怎麽？什麽是“错误 99”？
What's this? What's "Error 99"?
功率不足。
Not enough power.
在故障中，所有可用电源都被占用
In a breakdown,
all available power is seized
由主系统保持运行。
by the primary system to keep running.
我们需要所有这些力量来重新启动ADS。
We need all that power
to reactivate the ADS.
该系统的安全功能是什麽会杀死我们？
The system's safety feature
is what's gonna kill us?
答案是肯定的。
Of course.
- 我们如何获得更多权力？
- 我们不能。
- How do we get more power?
- We can't.
但我们可以重新分配我们所拥有的。
But we can redistribute what we have.
- 只需要...
- 关闭主系统。
- Just need to...
- Shut down the primary system.
- 是的。完全。
- 在哪儿?
- Yes. Exactly.
- Where is it?
- 呃，隔壁楼上。
- 我一起去。
- Uh, next floor up.
- I'm coming with you.
我们逃到了这里。
We escaped down here.
- 这是哪里？水处理中心？
- 水力发电系统。下八。
- Where is that? Water treatment center?
- Hydroelectric system. Sub eight.
给我八分锺。我能找到她。
Give me eight minutes.
I could find her.
等。现在是谁？
Wait. Who's this now?
试用版。蓝色的宝宝。
Beta. Blue's baby.
迅猛龙。
Velociraptor.
- 什麽?
- 小猛禽？
- What?
- A baby raptor?
你给她起了个名字。怎麽样？
You gave her a name.
How about that?
我答应了一下，我们会把她带回家。
I made a promise
we would bring her home.
你对恐龙许下了诺言。
You made a promise
to a dinosaur.
你和我们一起来，对吧？
You're coming with us, right?
麦茜，我...
Maisie, I...
请。
Please.
- 我将在第五频道。
- 好。
- I'll be on channel five.
- Okay.
我们在三个。
We're on three.
回来。
Come back.
我总是回来。
I always come back.
我会在十天内让那个直升机热。等待我的信号。
I'll have that chopper hot in ten.
Wait for my signal.
疏散阶段四完成。
Evacuation phase four complete.
所有生物资产现在都处于遏制状态。
All living assets now in containment.
加油。
Come on.
还做噩梦吗？
Still get nightmares?
一直以来。
All the time.
你?
You?
我有很多遗撼。
I have a lot of regrets.
哦,是的?
Oh, yeah?
嗯,
Well,
我们坚持后悔，我们停留在过去。
we hold on to regret,
we stay in the past.
我想，重要的是...
What matters, I guess, is...
这就是我们现在所做的。
Is what we do now.
- 正确的?
- 是的。
- Right?
- Yeah.
啊。
Ah.
好。
Okay.
没有人说会有虫子。
Nobody said there'd be bugs.
B4.她在这里。
B4. She's in here.
注意侧面。他们总是从侧面来。
Watch the sides.
They always come from the sides.
你知道，起初我们以为它们会把猎物排出肚子，但事实并非如此。
You know, at first we thought
they disembowel their prey, but no.
他们足够聪明，可以直接进入喉咙。
They're smart enough
to go straight for the throat.
静脉，动脉。
The veins, the arteries.
有时两者同时进行。
Sometimes both at the same time.
好。
Okay.
我们有你。它就在那条过道上。
We've got you.
It's right down that aisle.
它就在你所在的过道上。
It's right down that aisle where you are.
他们为什麽在...
Why are they skulking in...
你可以为它冲刺。
You can sprint right for it.
好。在这里。
Okay. Here it is.
好的，它将是六个网格上的黄色按钮。
Okay, it'll be a yellow button
on a grid of six.
有一个绿色按钮。是否看到绿色按钮？
There's a green button.
Do you see a green button?
它不是那个绿色按钮。
It's not that green button.
从底部开始是四个。在此之上...
It's four from the bottom.
Above this...
哇，哇，哇。第四个起来了吗？
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Fourth one up?
第三个向下或第四个向上。同样的事情。
Third one down or fourth one up.
Same thing.
伊恩，要具体。
Ian, be specific.
她在这里
She was here.
灯熄灭。
Lights off.
我不知道我怎麽可能更具体
I don't know how I could possibly
be more specific
除了说你想要的那个被标记
other than to say
that the one you want is marked
- 与“E1”。E1.
- E1.
- with "E1." E1.
E1.
是的。
Yeah.
不。不,不,不,不。
No. No, no, no, no.
该死。她很快。
Damn it. She's fast.
嘿!
Hey!
看着我。
Eyes on me.
我必须打她的脖子一侧。
I've got to hit her
on the side of her neck.
麦茜，你要把她的注意力放在心上。
Maisie,
you're gonna hold her focus.
授予
Grant,
我们是三角的。
we're triangulating.
去。
Go.
对不起，女孩
Sorry, girl.
我答应过妈，我会让你回家。
I promised your mom
I'd get you home.
主系统正在重新引导。
Primary system rebooting.
等。哦，不，不，不。
Wait. Oh, no, no, no.
- 不 不。
- 它正在重新启动。
- No, no, no.
- It's rebooting.
它不应该这样做。
It shouldn't be doing that.
来,拿这个
Here, take this.
- 会留在上面。
- 关闭它！
- Gonna stay on it.
- Shut it down!
我们将让它发挥作用。我们要弄清楚这一点。这很复杂。
We're gonna make it work.
We're gonna figure this out. It's complex.
我们没有时间进行复杂处理！
We don't have time for complex!
主系统已损坏。
Primary system compromised.
等一会。等一会。
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
空中威慑系统处于活动状态。
Aerial Deterrent System active.
胜利。胜利。
Victory. Victory.
该死的，感觉很好。
Damn, that felt good.
哦！加油！
Oh! Come on!
你的故事是什麽？
What's your story?
等!
Wait!
在生物科技，我们致力于这个想法
At Biosyn, we're dedicated to the idea
恐龙可以教会我们更多关于自己的知识。
that dinosaurs can teach us
more about ourselves.
好的，凯拉。我们一切准备就绪。
All right, Kayla. We're good to go.
好的，可爱的。
Okay, cutie.
过来这里。
Come here.
你没事吧?
You all right?
- 有一天。
- 好。
- Someday.
- Okay.
嘿。
Hey.
我记得你。
I remember you.
请。你必须听我说。
Please. You have to listen to me.
你制造了一场生态灾难。
You created an ecological disaster.
我可以修复它。
And I can fix it.
夏洛特·洛克伍德改变了麦茜身体的每一个细胞。
Charlotte Lockwood changed every cell
in Maisie's body.
它救了她的命。
It saved her life.
如果我能理解夏洛特是如何改写麦茜的DNA的
If I can understand
how Charlotte rewrote Maisie's DNA,
我可以把变化从一个蝗虫传播到整个蝗虫群。
I can spread change from one locust
to the entire swarm.
为时已晚。
Before it's too late.
没关系。
It's okay.
这是她想要的。
It's what she would've wanted.
谢谢。
Thank you.
不 不。
No, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no.
他?
Him?
不是他。不是他。总是他。
Not him. Not him.
It's always him.
每一个...
Every si...
那是你肩膀上的恐龙吗？
Is that a dinosaur
on your shoulder?
是的。为什麽?
Yeah. Why?
我有空气。在中心与我见面。
I have air. Meet me at the center.
不不不。等等。嘿 嘿。不要降落在这里。
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, hey. Do not land in here.
我别无选择，伙计。山谷并不安全。
I don't have a choice, dude.
The valley isn't safe.
不，他们不再在山谷里了！
No, they're not in the valley anymore!
哦!
Oh!
这与我们无关。
This isn't about us.
去!去!
Go! Go!
加油!
Come on!
哦，我的上帝！让他起来！快点，快点！
Oh, my God! Get him up!
Come on, come on!
加油。
Come on.
加油 加油 加油 加油。
Come on, come on, come on!
加油!
Come on!
艾莉，不！
Ellie, no!
来吧，麦茜！去！
Come on, Maisie! Go!
拉姆齐，进去。
Ramsay, get in.
加油 加油 加油。
Come on, come on, come on.
每个人都抱着某人。
Everybody hold on to somebody.
哦, 哦。
Ow.
不，在每个层面上。
No, at every level.
在行政队伍中彻底存在系统性腐败。
Complete systemic corruption
in the executive ranks.
“系统性腐败。你明白了吗？写下来。
"Systemic corruption." You get that?
Write that down.
是的，这太疯狂了。
Yeah, it's crazy.
然后。。。然后我们撞进了这个冰湖，对吧？
And then... And then we crashed
into this ice lake, right?
我的意思是，他们真的欠我一架飞机。
I mean,
they literally owe me a plane.
我需要在实验室对这个样本进行审查
I need to get this sample vetted
at the lab
在我把它带到我在《纽约时报》的联系人之前。
before I take it to my contact
at the Times.
你可以，呃，跟我来。
You could, uh, come with me.
除非你需要回到你的挖掘。
Unless you need
to get back to your dig.
- 艾莉?
- 是的?
- Ellie?
- Yeah?
我和你一起来。
I am coming with you.
我知道。再过一分钟，我们就会把你和你的乡亲们送回家。
I know. One more minute,
then we'll send you home with your folks.
今天是见证的第一天
Today marks the first day of testimony
来自生物科技举报人拉姆齐·科尔。
from Biosyn whistleblower Ramsay Cole.
参议院还将听取格兰特医生，萨特勒和玛律科姆的发言
The Senate will also hear from
Doctors Grant, Sattler and Malcolm,
自侏罗纪公园事件发生以来，他们一直在这场辩论中发声。
who have been vocal in this debate
since the incident at Jurassic Park.
你看起来。。。
You look...
- 难受。
- ...值得 信赖。
- Uncomfortable.
- ...trustworthy.
是的，不习惯它。
Yeah, not getting used to it.
让我们完成这个。
Let's finish this.
是的。
Yeah.
吴亨利博士找到了紧急解决方案
Dr. Henry Wu
has found an emergency solution
到生态危机。
to the ecological crisis.
他使用病原体来改变蝗虫的DNA
His use of a pathogen
to alter the locusts' DNA
彻底改变了现代遗传学。
has revolutionized modern genetics.
他将这一发现归功于另一位科学家夏洛特·洛克伍德。
He attributed the discovery
to another scientist, Charlotte Lockwood,
近13年前去世。
who died nearly 13 years ago.
根据联合国法令，生物科技山谷已被指定为全球保护区。
By UN decree, Biosyn valley
has been designated a global sanctuary.
动物们将自由地生活在那里，远离外界。
The animals will live there free,
safe from the outside world.
- 钱?
- 钱。
- Money?
- Money.
谢谢。
Thank you.
地球上的生命已经存在了数亿年。
Life on Earth has existed
for hundreds of millions of years.
而恐龙只是其中的一部分。
And dinosaurs were only a part of that.
而我们在这方面所占的比例甚至更小。
And we're an even smaller part of that.
他们真的让我们看到了。
They really put us in perspective.
地球上的生命在6500万年前就存在的想法......
The idea that life on Earth
existed 65 million years ago...
这是令人谦卑的。
it's humbling.
我们表现得好象我们独自一人在这里，但我们不是。
We act like we're alone here,
but we're not.
我们是一个由所有生物组成的脆弱系统的一部分。
We're part of a fragile system
made up of all living things.
如果我们要生存下来，我们必须相互信任。
If we're going to survive,
we'll have to trust each other.
相互依赖。
Depend on each other.
共存。
Coexist.